<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>help.koken.me :: Site publishing</title>
    <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/topics/696983-site-publishing</link>
    <description>Site publishing articles</description>
    <item>
      <title>public set with privat albums</title>
      <description>hi

is it possible to have a public albums page (without password protection) with all private albums within (with album cover picture) but all the private albums within are password protected?
I need this for the customer pictures I cannot publish public but I do not want that the customer needs to remember the albums address.

br Daniel</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 20:36:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14303420</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BIG space issues</title>
      <description>Hi,

I've just set up Koken using the Elementary theme and I have a large space on each page between the primary navigation at the top of the page and the page title/content. 

Can this be edited/closed down.

(Please note: Not the website title and the navigation which I have worked out how to increase/decrease using the 'Line Height' in page settings) 

Thanks
Jason


</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 10:16:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14259806</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to add links to my Clients page.....?</title>
      <description>I have a Clients page with links to their websites.

I created it when I first set up the site a few months ago.

I would now like to add some links to this page, but I cannot remember how to do it!

The Client links page is here&gt; http://www.denismortellphotography.ie/index.php?/pages/client-links/

How do I add links (in alphabetical order) to this?

Many thanks.

Denis</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Aug 2015 11:56:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14242060</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slow viewing of images</title>
      <description>Google analytics reports that viewing of my images requires an average of 5 seconds. Some viewers are reporting that this is too long and "my server not able to handle the traffic."  I'm using JustHost and all its applications are current. Speed Analytics report that there are javascripts that are interruping image rendering, but I can't find a setting in Koken to asynchronize this script and speed things up. Can you help?
JIM
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 21:32:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13852943</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting rid of file names</title>
      <description>How do I get it so that you can't see the file names in the upper tab of the browser when viewing images on my site?


Thanks,
S</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 21:07:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13312634</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valentino Rockstud Shoes We are also </title>
      <description>We have always enjoyed a good showhouse and anticipate that the ELLE DECOR Modern Life Concept House won't disappoint. Premiering in just a few weeks, the ELLE DECOR showhouse will feature 10 of ED's "Designers Valentino Shoes Outlet to Watch" and exquisite interiors. The designers will partner up with premier brands to create aweinspiring spaces. Sketches have already been released and we can only promise clean, minimalist designs. Click Here to purchase tickets. 
Want to Valentino Rockstud Shoes Sale read more? Stay up to date on all things design by following our Valentino Rockstud ShoesManhattan Interior Design Examiner page. We are also the National Interior Design Examiner. From traditional bridal shower brunches to vintageinspired tea parties,. 
Celebrate White Wine Day with various white wine http://www.valentinosalestore.com/ recipes August 4 is National White Wine Day. To celebrate here are white sangria recipes, white wine coolers, wine cocktails and wine spritzer recipes. 
http://www.cellphonecasesa.com/gucci-66plus-cases-c-82_180/
http://www.lhbon.com/gz-women-moccasins-c-48_55/
http://www.lhbon.com/kate-spade-satchel-c-111_114/
http://www.mulberrybagsale.com/mulberry-satchel-bags-c-23.html
http://www.cellphonecasesa.com/burberry-66plus-cases-c-82_172/
http://www.lhbon.com/celine-trio-c-13_25/
http://www.isabelmaranton.com/isabel-marant-sneakers-c-5.html
http://www.mulberrybagsale.com/mulberry-tote-bags-c-28.html</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Aug 2015 08:33:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13307362</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>louis vuitton handbags online she made</title>
      <description>carb alkaline diet and yoga workout tips
Elle Macpherson is superfit at 51, thanks to an alcoholfree, low carb alkaline diet and regular workouts that include yoga, Pilates and running. Macpherson said she has aged well because louis vuitton handbags online she made health and fitness a priority many years ago.
"In my 40s, I started to focus on health and wellness," Elle told Ocean Drive. "I stopped drinking 'alcohol] and taking any drugs even aspirin and I began really cleaning out my system."
As a result of clean living, an organic alkaline diet and daily exercise, Elle said turning 50 wasn't traumatic emotionally or physically, as it is for http://www.lhbon.com/louis-vuitton-c-86/ many people.
"By the time I hit 50, I didn't feel any sort of plateau physically, and it didn't feel like a shock emotionally either," said Macpherson. "It wasn't like, 'Oh my gosh, I'd better get myself together before I turn 50.' It was more like I was reborn."
Macpherson, who was nicknamed "The Body" during her modeling heyday, has redefined middle age, but admits she works hard to maintain her agedefying beauty. Elle said her low carb alkaline diet consists mostly of "vegetables, a little bit of fish, not much protein, and no coffee or alcohol."
Elle said her health improved shortly changes after she switched to the alkaline diet. "I noticed changes in just two weeks," said Macpherson. "I had more vitality, my skin wasn't dry. I stopped craving sugar, my mood stabilized, everything became more balanced. A welcome byproduct was losing weight around my middle."
The alkaline diet, which Victoria Beckham also follows, includes fresh green vegetables, fruits, beans, lentils, spices, seeds and nuts. The theory is that eating a diet high in alkalineproducing foods minimizes inflammation by reducing acid buildup in our bodies (inflammation fuels aging and weight gain). Foods to avoid include sugar, coffee, alcohol, processed foods and dairy.
Elle said her other antiaging beauty secrets include lots of water (she drinks three liters every day), exfoliating louis vuitton bags for sale her skin, moisturizing every day, and sleeping for a minimum of eight hours a night. No matter what, Macpherson makes a point to exercise every day, both for her physical and emotional health. "I can't ever remember doing something physical and feeling worse," she said.
Macpherson said she's comfortable with getting older and has no desire to be young again. Elle, who has not gone overboard with much (or any) plastic surgery, said she prefers prefer to age naturally.
"'Beauty at every age' is such a boring clich, but beauty is not just reserved for youth," Elle said. "There's a big movement that supports that. I didn't feel any kind of milestone pressure turning 50, perhaps because I've been preparing for this stage of my life for a long time."Bobbi Kristina deathbed photo sold for $100,000: Bobbi lies in funeral casketBobbi louis vuitton bags on sale Kristina Brown's deathbed photos showing her in a funeral casket have been sold to a tabloid for over $100,000. The deathbed photo was taken at Bobbi Kristina's wake, a day before her Aug. 1.
Discover the world of snakes with at Benjamin Banneker Historical ParkCold blooded snakes love the hot summer weather as they are able to move about more easily. Unfortunately, we associate their cold bloodedness with being evil.
http://www.lhbon.com/balenciaga-purses-c-3_12/
http://www.lhbon.com/monogram-empreinte-c-86_96/
http://www.airjordanmvp.com/air-jordan-xx9-c-96/
http://www.lhbon.com/valentino-pumps-c-150_151/
http://www.lhbon.com/balenciaga-part-time-c-3_7/
http://www.isabelmaranton.com/
http://www.cellphonecasesa.com/nhl-iphone-6-cases-c-249_275/
http://www.cellphonecasesa.com/samsung-s4-cases-c-84/</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Aug 2015 05:11:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13252203</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Displaying only Featured Albums on the frontpage</title>
      <description>I would like to have featured albums on the frontpage, but not others. The Other public Albums should be included in Essays but otherwise not show up on the page.

How can I do that? I am using the Chastain Theme currently.

</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 15:40:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13079176</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using "Favorites "to display photos with the Boulevard theme -images not showing up in google search</title>
      <description>hello, 

i built my website using the boulevard theme and used "favorites" to display a stream of photos. the photos have keywords with my name and descriptions but still don't show up when i google search my name. the website shows up as about #5 on google search and #1 on other search engines. seems like the images should be appearing?


thanks!</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 15:17:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13076439</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Techno Jaya Store</title>
      <description>Hey guy,
Techno Jaya Store here, exporting Camera Digital | Copy Paper | Shave/Razor | Fishing Reels | Abu Garcia | Accurate | Daiwa | Miya | Epoch | Okuma | Penn | Shimano | Van Staal | ZeeBaaS
Visit our website, let's talk details. http://technojayastore.com</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2015 00:40:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13062549</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using a different slider with Koken</title>
      <description>Would it be possible to use a different slider than Pulse to display slideshows? Something like WOWSlider or FlexSlider? And would that be accomplished using a theme or a plugin?</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 14:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13056255</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Frontpage</title>
      <description>Hi,
how can I make frontpage with one of my Pictures in Fullscreen? 
I want a Picture in when someones enters my Page. How can I Do it with the  Regale2 Template?

THX! 
Ersin</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 13:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13043019</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Valentino Shoes Outlet tablespoon</title>
      <description>Midnight Pudding http://www.valentinosalestore.com/ Recipe 
Bring on the night by melting the semisweet chocolate in the top half of a double boiler over medium heat. Stir the chocolate constantly with a rubber spatula until it is completely melted and smooth, then remove from the heat and set aside. Heat the halfandhalf, 1/4 cup sugar, and the cocoa in a 3quart saucepan over mediumhigh heat. When hot, Valentino Shoes On Salewhisk to dissolve the sugar. Bring to a boil. While the cream is heating, whisk the egg yolks, remaining sugar and cornstarch in a medium bowl until slightly thickened and lemoncolored. Pour the boiling halfandhalf mixture slowly into the egg yolks and stir to combine. Return the mixture to the saucepan and heat over mediumhigh heat, stirring constantly, until it begins to boil and becomes quite thick, about 30 seconds. Remove the pan from the heat and transfer the mixture to a large bowl. Add the melted chocolate, then place the bowl in ice water and stir the pudding until it is cold. Fold all but 2 tablespoons of chopped white chocolate into the pudding. Portion 3/4 cup of the pudding into each of 4 dessert dishes and sprinkle 1/2 Valentino Shoes Outlet tablespoon of the remaining white chocolate over the top of each. </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 00:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13040076</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hide tags</title>
      <description>How can i hide the tags for albums or sets? 
I don´t want to see them on the published webside.
http://alles-ausm-kopf.de/albums/matti/</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 09:51:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13025768</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vimeo videos not appearing</title>
      <description>Hi,

Thanks so much for your great service.

I edit one of the pages of www.anadelgadomartins.com and now I'm not able to insert vimeo videos. It all seems ok at koken administration panel but the videos don't appear online.

It's the "Ficção" page.

Thanks.

Best regards,
Marcos</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 10:44:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13019904</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hosting</title>
      <description>Will the software work with business catalyst?
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2015 11:52:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12975899</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom Page Adress</title>
      <description>Hi! How can I publish my links as "site.com/pagename" not "site.com/pages/pagename"?</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 16:33:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12969065</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desktop view is fine, mobile isnt</title>
      <description>Hello 

I'm bulding my little website using the "boulevard" theme. I've added few  comments to the custom css:
http://www.pic-upload.de/view-27595532/css.png.html

I've moved the site title and the navigation on the same line, using " position: relative;  bottom: 45px;". I know it isnt optimal, but thats how far I got with my understanding...

To the problem:
This is how it looks on a desktop: http://www.pic-upload.de/view-27595531/desktop.png.html
This is how it looks on a mobile device: http://www.pic-upload.de/view-27595533/mobile.png.html

As you can see the site title is over the navigation, pretty useless what I've crafted here...


Can any one help me to get this working on one line on mobile devices too?

Cheers Josh</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 11:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12926581</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Logo issues on elementary theme</title>
      <description>It's been almost a year I'm using koken and the "elementary" theme which has been working great for me.

However my logo disappeared from my website and it seems if I'm not mistaken that I do not have the feature of inserting a logo anymore...
I used to go on site settings in order to insert a link where was uploaded my logo. Now there's no settings available for the theme or the template.
Is that normal?

Could you tell me more about it? 

Thanks for your time,

Sincerely

Phi-Haï
www.shotwitheyes.fr


</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2015 18:59:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12887501</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can I display images with no text underneath?</title>
      <description>Is it possible to have images appear on my site with nothing else on the screen other than the &lt;&gt; arrows at each side of the image.

At the moment, my images are appearing with name of the category folder that they have been assigned to, as well as their number within the folder, at the bottom of the image.

I would like my image on the screen - nothing else.

Possible?

Thanks.

D.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2015 21:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12878264</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Links do not work</title>
      <description>Hi!

After updating to 0.21.2 links to albums do not work anymore, I've tried deleting old ones and creating new links, cleaning images and system cache, different image processing software and labels and links options...

Only default home page displays correctly. I'm using Boulevard theme, but I get the same error with the Elementary template. Tried several browsers as well: Chrome, Firefox, Android and Safari (mobile)

My site:

josetorre.com

Thanks!</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 10:58:06 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12877921</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trouble by updating the frontend?</title>
      <description>I did make some changes in the stettings for page title and tag and added a new album. But the changes will not display in the frontend? I dont now why. (dumzeugs.de)</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 11:18:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12875441</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adjusting Summary font-size in Regale Albums page</title>
      <description>Hi, I'm trying to do the above but I can't get the right css code to do the trick. Can you shed some light on the code please?</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 21:45:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12863279</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>caption in the lightbox</title>
      <description>Hello,

I'm a member of koken since 2 month now, I plan to launch my new web site in a few days but I've a little problem that I can't resolve.
In the lightbox, the picture is runing but under the image, the title of the site and the title of the albums is still appearing. I want to make it desapear, and just to have written "captions" if the user want to know the caption.
Please have a look: http://www.nanda-gonzague.com/koken/albums/hayastan/content/01-works-hayastan/lightbox/

How can I do to customize it please? 
I've read a lot of FAQ and forum but nothing possible until now.

Thanks and best regards.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2015 19:02:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12861145</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publishing Pillar by row height?</title>
      <description>Could Pillar be modified to publish with a fixed row height that all images (portrait &amp; landscape) fit into? It could also contain variable row height like what is currently available with column width. The reason I ask is because with the current setup portrait images are published much larger than landscape images. </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2015 18:39:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12829737</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loopback Connections</title>
      <description>Dear Sir,

I am wanting to install Koken on my ReadyNAS 104. The installation has gone fine but, while site publishing it gives an API Error as under:

API Error

The theme is not able to make contact with your Koken installation. Contact your host to see if they are blocking loopback connections.

Could you help me how to get over the error</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 22:08:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12828648</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple sites?</title>
      <description>Can Koken be used like SlideShow Pro Director to feed media to different sites/domains?</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 01:15:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12810248</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Part of my template don't show right in Google Chrome</title>
      <description>Dear Sir/Madam,

Today I encountered a problem with my the way part of my potfolio looked. I am usuing a Boulevard template for my photography portfolio. If you go to (for example) irynayeroshko.com --&gt; Photography --&gt; Faces http://irynayeroshko.com/albums/faces/ , you will see that apart from the general side scroll (if this is a name for it), there is a picture below that doesn't fit in. You can see it in other photo folders, too, except Free Picture - everything seems fine there.
This problem, however, doesn't occur with other browsers. 
I wonder what it wrong and how it can be fixed.
I haven't changed anything before with my Site settings neither with Chrome settings.
I have cleared cache several times but it didn't help.

Looking forward to hear from you,

Ira</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 19:32:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12797811</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Images as links</title>
      <description>Hi There 

Im really keen to know if I can change the links in the left hand menu of my website to small images? I would love to be able to use images that incorporate with my branding and logo and use them as links to my albums - opposed to the standard text links... 

Im using Madison 2 as my site theme.

Best,
Thomas</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 10:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12768961</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Create a client area link with Password Protect</title>
      <description>I purchased the password protect plugin.  Ultimately what I would like to do is have a client visit my site and click on the link named Client Area.  Depending on the password it will go to there specific album.   If you have other ideas other than emailing a link, please let me know.

Similar to this:

http://www.charmainetoews.com/index2.php#/proofing/

Thanks!
Crystal</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 14:53:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12748257</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Home" Text on main page</title>
      <description>On the main page of crystaldphotography.ca, there is a text "Home" on top of my picture.   How do I remove that?

Thanks
Crystal</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 15:08:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12748152</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>working with chrome</title>
      <description>there is a problem with opening pages in google chrome. the last picture is not in the line.
 how to fix?</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2015 19:34:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12747200</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changing URL</title>
      <description>I've done quite a bit of reading trying to sort this out myself, but I can't change my URL, and Im hoping you can PLEEEASE help me.
My koken site is currently at vanessasize.com/vanessa 
but I need it to be vanessasize.com.au

I've tried editing the htaccess file, but I don't really know what I'm doing so that hasn't helped!

I'd really appreciate any help as I have spent many hours including a complete re-install and design to try and sort it myself.

(I have redirected my vanessasize.com.au to vanessasize.com/vanessa for now as my other site has gone since I tried installing this one!)
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 May 2015 08:17:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12747135</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change Content Link URL</title>
      <description>Hey guys,

i created a new link under the site section for content. The generated link looked like: http://www.url.com/contentlinkname/

I deleted the link and later added it back under the same link name. The URL looked like: http://www.url.com/contentlinkname-1/

The same procedure again and now the domain is: http://www.url.com/contentlinkname-2/

How can I get rid of the numeration and get back to a clean URL without the numbers?

Best regards,
Stefan</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 10:34:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12738108</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where did my sites go????  Now both are missing... HELP!!!</title>
      <description>OK, I insist on asking things in this online emptiness, hoping someone has real useful answers.

This time, without getting my questions answered in any reasonable way, I just decided to go "by the book" to transfer the Koken site and turn it into my root site, this, moving from jorgeparra/com/koken into jorgeparra.com

So far, after 3 hours of the koken control panel saying it is "saving " the changes, what I have now is that neither the new, woken site nor my oldster are showing online. Today I have nada!!

I need assistance as to what do I have to do now.

thanks
 </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 19:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12711205</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embed koken galleries into an existing site?</title>
      <description>Hello,
I'm wondering if it is possible to create galleries in Koken and then embed them into an existing site?
Or am I required to use a template?

Basically I want to use this in the same way as Slideshow Pro Server used to work.
Is this possible?

I looked through similar questions but didn't see a definitive answer.

Thanks for your time!

--Z
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 09:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12711152</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filtering data: problem with pagination</title>
      <description>Hi there!
I'm trying to use:

To filter out every image within the category "Editorials" this works: but my infinite="true" stops working!

I believe the fault is in the {{ location.parameters.page }} but i have no clue how to solve it!</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 15:39:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12709682</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Site preview in admin broken?</title>
      <description>When using Admin-&gt;Site to preview my site: it dosent show any images!
Sounds like http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/5256906-preview-php-hs but i cant find any solution available.
It's not a big problem since i know what my site look like: but it would be nice to have it functional...

To make it even more strange: my local dev site (with out "pretty urls") displays correct :shock: 

Any one got some insight to what can wrong?

To be clear using the url: http://somedomain.com/admin/#/site/draft/theme/url:/album/ no album covers
Using the url http://somedomain.com/preview.php?/album/&amp;preview=norma Album covers shows as they should</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 19:56:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12639169</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moving the token site to my root domain address / URGENT HELP!</title>
      <description>Hello. I read in the Admin section of the Koken control panel that this process seems to be simple. 

The section called " Site URL" explains this: 

"Defines the URL your Koken site is viewed with. You may edit this to your domain root or to a specific directory. If an assigned directory doesn't exist, Koken will create it for you." 

I need more precise instructions to do this. It sounds all too vague to me, specially after reading users comments about loosing all their original content ( something apparently related with a replaced htaccess file that is created by koken.

I have not yet tried anything, but I am ready to move my site, using Madison 2 ( jorgeparra.com/koken) to become the main site ( jorgeparra.com), but I want to make sure I do it the right way, and I need assistance with that.

Many thanks!

Jorge</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 19:53:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12630573</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publishing more than one homepage</title>
      <description>Hi. I really like how everything functions for the Regale 2 theme. Notably, the home page with sliding images, and the simple &amp; clean links to photos and/or video. I was wondering, is there a way to publish multiple, mini-sites (home page with 2-3 simple links to Info, Photo &amp; Video) within one website. For example: 

MAIN HOME PAGE 
&gt; Link 1 &gt; Home Page + Info Link + Photos Link + Video Link
&gt; Link 2 &gt; Home Page + Info Link + Photos Link + Video Link       
&gt; Link 3 &gt; Home Page + Info Link + Photos Link + Video Link       

I wouldn't even need any links on the main home page to Link 1, Link 2 or Link 3.
I'd just be using the url's from each Link created.
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 17:57:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12449116</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Breadcrumb link should return user to the originating page in the album, not the top of the album</title>
      <description>Hi Everyone,

I've got a question/feature request regarding pagination and breadcrumbs. Currently, when a user views an image from an album and breadcrumbs are enabled, the link inside the breadcrumbs leads back to page 1 of the album, not the page containing the image the user clicked on. Is there a way around this or is this just how Koken's breadcrumbs and pagination work right now?

And by the way, this is using the Elementary theme for a client asset delivery website.

Thanks,
Brett</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 14:21:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12436605</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Selling work online</title>
      <description>Hi guys, 

Love your work as always! I was wondering though... 

Does Koken have the capability to allow someone to set up an online store? As a professional photographer I would LOVE the ability to direct customers directly to a section of my site that allowed me to go about the process of offering the purchase of my images to print online with an attached payment system and wot not.

If not would it be something that Koken might be in the process of developing for the future?

Regards,
Thomas</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 17:54:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12402161</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Render Blocking</title>
      <description>Hi, I'd like to know if there are any ways to optimise my website speed while using Koken. I checked out my page speed (link below) and the biggest problem seems to be render blocking. Is this fixable or just something we have to roll with ATM?

Thanks.

Grant

 https://developers.google.com/speed/pagespeed/insights/?url=grantkimages.com&amp;tab=mobile </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 14:46:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12258401</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Load website back to koken</title>
      <description>I`ve already made some basic stuff for a koken website with a friend, who helped me. Then I`ve made many changes in the Koken admin User interface. But it did not work at all, since I used IE 11. I then tried in Firefox and it worked, but it also showed that some stuff was already messed up by what I`ve done in IE 11. BUT, I have not published the changes. So my website is still how it was a a day before. Can I load the website back into the Koken UI, so that both are "in sync". So I do not want to load from Koken to the Web, but vice versa.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 16:46:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12224509</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pre-Caching Uploaded Images? Part 2</title>
      <description>I'm going to offer a possible solution to people who wanted to rebuild all their images caches so the first site visitors don't have to wait for the server to render the images.  The thread I was responding to had a "This question has received the maximum number of answers." On it though, so I thought I'd just start a new one.

It's possible to use a utility like wget running on your own local computer to simply access every link on your website and trigger the cache build.  http://www.guyrutenberg.com/2014/05/02/make-offline-mirror-of-a-site-using-wget/  Wget can be installed in osx from macports or brew.  Wget is also available for windows.  It's included with most linux distributions as well.   

Basically wget downloads a copy of your website, so all images will be built.  I run it after making major changes and it works well.  There may also be other utilities that download entire websites which will work as well.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 01:12:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11683970</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>from the witches celine bag to</title>
      <description>Fantasy holds a special place in the hearts of everyone, be it adults or children. The legend of the tooth fairy recounts the tale of a magical fairy who awards the children for the teeth that have fallen off. So every time your tooth broke off, you would place it under the pillow and lo and behold! the next morning you would be awarded with money and little treats. Of course, sometimes the kind fairy would allow your parents to keep the tooth while rewarding you as well. This magical fairy also provides the inspiration for very beautiful Halloween costumes for kids and equally hilariously funny costume ideas for adults. For the costume, you can include a white or pink corset tops, "poofy" skirts with trims, tiara, and shimmery wings. Not to forget, a sequined fairy tooth wand. This hilariously funny costume can lighten the mood in any room with its outrageous looking white imprinted tank top, a pair of white shorts, a pair of white wings, and a headpiece made of molar cutouts. My sixyearold niece wanted to dress up as a tooth fairy last Halloween. Dressed up in a gorgeous poofy dress, a tiara, matching fairy slippers, and beautiful sequined wings, she looked an adorable darling. Tooth fairy costumes with the wings and the tulles skirts are fairly easy to make.

For making this beautiful costume, select a big poofy white dress. Alternately, you can make your very own fairy tutu by measuring and cutting the tulle and attaching them to an elastic in a 'U' shape. Now sew in the toothbrushes and floss packs onto your [b]http://www.celinehandbagse.com/ [/b] skirt. For the fairy necklace, thread the gum onto a piece of string. Wings for your little tooth fairy can be made of poster boards and covered with glitter foil. Attach strings to secure it over the shoulders. A magical fairy wand, a bag of fake cold coins, and a tiara made of teeth can complete the look of the perfect tooth fairy.

The origin of the tooth fairy is a mystery with some attributing it to an old European tradition where the teeth of little children was buried and hidden from the witches to prevent them from being cursed. This tradition was carried on as children began hiding their teeth under the pillow, expecting gifts and money from the tooth fairy. [b][url=http://www.celinehandbagse.com/]celine bag[/url][/b] The fancy tooth fairy costumes are a great way of having loads of fun this Halloween.
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 03:38:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11677511</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Images not loading - entire site now has spinning circles instead of images?!</title>
      <description>I have sorted the problem regarding the URL in Settings/Site Publishing.

However, I now have another problem.

All my images - all those in Library and sub-menus, and on the live site are not loading. They are just spinning circles.

I have tried the fix of changing processing in Settings/Image Publishing (by the way, I only see two choices, ImageMagick 6.2.8 and GD Bundled (2.1.0 compatible), not 5 as listed in the Help article) and they don't work. Still spinning circles all over. (I did clear the image cache also after changing the selection.) 

I've also tried uploading a new image to see if it appears - it won't upload at all.

Help!!!!

Thanks.

Denis</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2015 10:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11668579</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>title image</title>
      <description>I want to change the site title; text to image.(for example, my hand script image of my name)
Can i do it?
If it could be, please tell me where should I upload the image and html code.

</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2015 06:45:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11668052</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannot edit URL in Site Publishing...?</title>
      <description>In Settings/Site Publishing I cannot edit the URL that I used to create my site to the URL that I am now using for the live site.

This means that I cannot edit the live site.

How can I edit the URL?

Thanks.

Denis</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 16:27:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11665179</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unlisted image are shown in content and lightbox view</title>
      <description>Hi the koken team, 

I've a problem with unlisted images.

In the album page everything is OK, the images aren't listed.

But in content view and lightbox view the images are listed

Regards, 

Chris</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 08:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11664389</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using CSS/HTML Class/ID selectors in Elementary Theme</title>
      <description>I am trying to edit some specific paragraphs in the HTML of my Elementary theme using class/id selectors in the css/html editor but I cannot see the changes or if it works. Are you able to do this in the Elementary theme?

example: (using comment format just for the question forum)

html would be: Base --&gt;
 and CSS would be */ #base{ font-size: 5em;} /*</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 01:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11664234</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full HTTPS in RSS feeds?</title>
      <description>My entire gallery is HTTPS but the RSS feed is generating HTTP links.

https://flexinno.com/portfolio/

https://flexinno.com/portfolio/feed/content/recent.rss

How do I force all the RSS feed generated links to be HTTPS like the rest of the gallery?

It's messing with my main site EV SSL when I stream Koken RSS content because none of it is secure, even though it's on the same domain.

https://flexinno.com </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2015 14:20:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11660147</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>cheap beats by dre Psychosis</title>
      <description>Cons of Medical Marijuana beats pill 
The use of marijuana to treat medical conditions has been debated by health care experts, both having significant clinical claims for and against its use. Medical marijuana can help to stimulate appetite in cancer and AIDS patients. It also helps to alleviate some of the symptoms of glaucoma and multiple sclerosis. Although medical marijuana beats by dre headphones on sale is generally favored by its patients, there are several arguments against its medical use and effectiveness. The arguments against the use of medical marijuana include the increased risk of psychosis, inferior effectiveness in treating glaucoma and increased risk in developing certain types of cancer. 
Increased Risk of cheap beats by dre Psychosis 
One of the arguments against the use of medical marijuana centers around its increased risk of both acute cheap beats by dre headphones psychosis and chronic mental illness, including schizophrenia. Marijuana is a powerful psychoactive drug and can have serious effects on the mind and body outside of its intended medical use. Some of the psychoactive side effects of using marijuana include hallucination, anxiety, memory loss and confusion. In the August 2007 issue of "The Lancet," Dr. Stanley Zammit and associates found a strong significant relationship between marijuana use and increased risk of psychosis, including severe anxiety, depression and suicidal tendencies. Dr. Sonija Luzi and associates, at the Institute of Psychiatry in London, state that two primary chemical agents found in marijuana, tetrahydrocannabinol and endocannabinoids, proved largely responsible for inducing the psychotic symptoms in marijuana users. 
Inferior Treatment beats wireless of Glaucoma 
Marijuana has been associated with treating glaucoma, an eye disease, since the 1970's. The National Eye Institute states that early studies showed that marijuana smoke lowered the cheap beats by dre studiointernal pressure inside the eye caused by glaucoma. In its early interventions in the 1970's, marijuana proved beneficial in treating the disease, but new medications and treatments have rendered marijuana as an inferior choice for this particular disease. Current treatments employ medications approved by the Food and Drug Association as well as laser surgery. The side effects of medical marijuana such as increased heart rate and decreased blood pressure have raised concerns cheap beats by dre mixr headphones that it may not be the most effective current choice for treating glaucoma. 
Increased Risk of beats by dre pro headphones sale Certain Cancers 
Another argument against the use of medical marijuana asserts that marijuana increases the risk of developing certain types of cancer such as lung and testicular cancer. The National Institute on Drug Abuse states that marijuana smoke can cause cancer of the respiratory tract because of the irritants and carcinogens it contains. They stated that marijuana smoke contains 50 to 70 percent more carcinogenic hydrocarbons than tobacco smoke. In addition, they stated that one of the active ingredients in marijuana, tetrahydrocannabinol, was significantly associated with respiratory infection and tumor growth. In addition, a study by Dr. Stephen Schwatz and associates at the beats by dre solo hd headphones Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center found that smoking marijuana increased the chances of developing testicular cancer by about 70 percent. One of the reasons why marijuana may cause cancer is because it is significantly linked to DNA damage, which may initiate tumor growth, according to Dr. Rajinder Singh and associates at the Cancer Biomarkers and Prevention Group in Sweden. 
http://www.hjbon.com/moncler-women-coats-c-72_74/
http://www.balenciagatop.com/
http://www.garebibber.com/
http://www.airjordanhot.com/air-jordan-4-shoes-9/
http://www.airjordanon.com/air-jordan-9-c-71/
http://www.limitedbeatsbydre.com/beats-by-dre-wireless-c-28/
http://www.celinehandbagse.com/celine-trapeze-c-71/</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 11:41:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11657584</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Body add code</title>
      <description>Hello, First, congratulations on track and to become an excellent application.

- I need to add code to third parties applications in code (BODY) Where is it found?

I await your response.
Best regards and thank you very much</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 10:36:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11653578</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to add TAGS to RSS feeds</title>
      <description>How can I add an image's TAGS to the Recent.rss ?

Is it a simple modification?

Thanks,
Matt</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2015 13:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11652540</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Size of images displayed in album view</title>
      <description>Hi, 

I am trying to modify the size and setup of images being displayed in album view. In all themes I have checked the images are displayed 1 per line and rather huge - already in the same size as if there were displayed as single image, i.e. leaving no reason for the user to actually switch to single image view at all. I would like to have them more in a thumbnail style, e.g. 3 or 4 per line, clearly smaller than in single image view. However, there does not seem to be a setting in Koken to modify the image size at all, right? I have found vague hints to modify this using the CSS editing possibilities but not how. 

For example, when using the default "timeline" view, there is a similar way of displaying images smaller and more than one in a row. However, I do not need a timeline view for my web site and have therefore removed it, but is there a way to use the same setup for album view? 

Thanks a lot, 
Tim</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 10:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11650333</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightbox in madison 2</title>
      <description>Hello,
i bought the theme "madison 2". is it possible to disable the lightbox? i do not wont the link to the lightbox when i klick on images.

thank you and best regards
Robert Buergel</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 09:50:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11650210</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Link on Website</title>
      <description>GM,
With your website can I add a link to a news article on the front page? I would like to put that article on our front page of our website. 
Thank you,
Bobby Flores

http://www.pe.com/articles/valley-765177-murrieta-grand.html</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2015 15:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11648557</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Fullscreen Slideshows?</title>
      <description>From the best I can tell, there are only two of the paid themes (Madison 2 &amp; Regale 2) that allow a full page slideshow (only the splash page).  I would like to have multiple full screen slideshows on my site.  Is that possible on any of the themes?  </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2015 21:04:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11646882</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Albums in categories</title>
      <description>Hello,

I'm using Axis theme and I would like to something like this : http://img11.hostingpics.net/pics/184841koken.jpg

I tried to create an album template by I only can filter items by one category.

Do you have any idea?

Thank you so much</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2015 16:08:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11645119</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do I put content under different pages</title>
      <description>Hi

It might be the simplest thing but I cannot work out how to put different images under different pages. Under the site tab I have say page1, page2, page3. How do I take the images and put them in different pages. At the moment I have them all on the home page and within libabry tab they are all under the 'content' tab. 

Thing is I don't see page1,page2,page3 under the the Libby tab but they exist in the 'Site' tab.

Thanks
Sherry</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 17:34:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11638038</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>site title</title>
      <description>Hi

How do i get rid of my site title /koken?
Everybody who's using koken.me doesn't have that. Why do I have it?
If you enter www.lauraknipsael.com it automaticly appears. 

Can you please help me this time?
Months ago I also send an email but never got any reply back..

Thanks a lot, 
Laura Knipsael </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Apr 2015 13:23:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11623245</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Removing Social Share from Lightbox</title>
      <description>Hi, firstly thanks for a great cms system geared for galleries. 

I have gone through both theme and template setting for all my pages and have successfully turned off the social share icons. The only place I have not been able to remove them from is when users view an album using lightbox. Is there a way to disable this feature?

Many Thanks.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 14:55:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11617230</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>photograph titles</title>
      <description>Hello,

I am using Boulevard Theme. I was wondering if there is a way I can set the imported images to automatically add the file name / alt tag to the caption. This would be great as I have large volumes of images to upload and adding the image titles for each image is not convenient at all for my workflow...

Are the theme template files available to edit incase inserting some php into the span would be the best solution?
 
Any ideas would be great to know !

Thank

david 

</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 17:12:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11613379</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changing site URL does not work</title>
      <description>Hi,

When I try and remove /koken/ from the site URL under site publishing it does not change and after clicking save it puts /koken/ back into the URL.

How can I make it so that it will accept the site root URL?

I am running it on a Windows Server 2012 R2 machine and IIS 8. Are there specific folder permissions I need to set?

Thanks</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 13:45:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11606596</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My site will not publish to my domain.</title>
      <description>Hi Koken

My site will only publish to www.deannapizzitelli.com/koken, and directly to my domain. 

Can you help?

Best, 
D</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Apr 2015 22:02:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11606551</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Display images on a page in mosaic/grid format</title>
      <description>*Sorry, I posted this already in the wrong category so I moved It here*

Is it possible to display a list of essays as if they were photos in an album... with a small thumbnail as a preview?

or alternatively, would it be possible to display photos on a custom page in a grid/mosaic fashion that has multiple rows and columns, which I can then link each image to a certain essay? At the moment I can only display essentially one column of images.

I hope I'm describing this well enough, and I've attached a link to to what I have set up now.

http://www.camden-thrasher.com/exp/koken/pages/recent/</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 01:19:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11600390</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>covers in featured albums</title>
      <description>Hello,

I've moved a couple of album from their primary category "album" also in the one "featured album". Doing this covers stopped to alternate when cursor passes over ..is there a particular reason? can I fix this?

many thanks

Bambi K

</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2015 15:56:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11594391</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embedding entire albums or galleries into a predesignated website.</title>
      <description>Is it possible to embed an album into another page?  For instance, I built a site already and want to use Koken as a tool to create a web gallery/album and then place this album into a jQuery Tab on a site that I have hand coded.  Is this possible?  I'm struggling to find a tool as powerful as Koken that has this feature.  I would love to be able to click to generate an embed script for my site.   
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Apr 2015 15:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11594188</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Koken + Cloudflare + Google Chrome</title>
      <description>Hi koken team, 

I have configured cloudflare to display my website faster and there is a problem with koken and google chrome.

My website is properly displayed on Firefox or Safari but there is no album displayed on google chrome

You have to reload the webpage to see that page correctly.

Regards, 

Chris</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 00:43:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11591042</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Koken hosting</title>
      <description>Hello, 

For your information, I've bought the domaine name "koken.website" today to allow user to host their website.

Price will be, I think, not expensive : 30€/year with 3rd level domain, and around 50€/year, with domaine name (.com, be, fr, etc), 1gb disk space max and email adress  and, Koken installed, for sure !! :)

Thanks a lot for your wonderfull CMS !!

Frédéric 
http://www.frch.be/
http://www.diamond-valley.com/</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 22:14:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11585061</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Admin page cannot charge</title>
      <description>Hi, 

Tryng to administrate my page bu the site http://****************.be/koken/admin dont load... I'm juste having a black page.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 12:34:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11582142</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changing site design</title>
      <description>Hi - I wonder if anyone can help.

I've designed a site, published it and it is active. However, I now want to COMPLETELY change the design to a new version, but it's likely to take me some time to develop as it's a going to be a bit customised.

If I change the URL in Site Publishing to a temporary directory whilst I work on the new design, will the active site remain working until the new one is ready, as obviously I don't want to replace the existing site until the new one is ready.

I have asked Koken (twice) this question - but it seems they are too busy to answer.

Many thanks for any help.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 21:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11581442</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Images Not Appearing</title>
      <description>In the Edit panel (Texts/Drafts) I am seeing five images which do not appear in the preview. If I publish the essay the images still do not appear.  I have restarted, emptied cache, reloaded, many times. Nothing I try will make the images appear.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 14:14:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11577139</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spin Wheel - change colors?</title>
      <description>Is it possible to change the colors of the spin wheel that appears when the site is loading an image?  </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 16:48:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11561816</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Api cache disk space</title>
      <description>Lookin disk usage in my cpanel I found that API cache is takin most of the disk space. Images folder using 13 MB, but api cache is 400 MB. What going on?</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2015 05:38:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11560183</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Editing recent rss or have imageUrl in it</title>
      <description>Is there any way to have raw imageUrl in rss feed.

I`m using Modx CMS and want to grab recent images in front page. Now I use content placeholder, but it renders some unnecessary tags.

With imageUrl placeholder I got more control how to render image in front page of my site.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 19:11:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11558672</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>individual album feeds not working in my site</title>
      <description>In the RSS doc it says there's an recent.rss feed for any published album, but this isn't working in my site. The main RSS feeds (essays, timeline, content) work OK. Have I missed something?

Thanks</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2015 06:58:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11556486</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Suggestion: assign custom .lens templates to albums or sets</title>
      <description>I think it would be great if we could assign different templates to albums or sets.

For example, i would need diffent layouts for private albums and public albums.

I found a related thread from 2013:

http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/2805768-custom-lens-template-for-different-albums

Maybe this could be done someday?</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 14:42:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11553162</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to make the albums the main page</title>
      <description>How can I make the albums directly my homepage?
I have seen the option under the Site menu, but it's not working as I want it to.

When I click on Home in the breadcrumb menu I want to go directly to the albums and not to some other page. Please help. Setting up redirects to try to bypass this problem also didn't help me much. </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 04:29:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11551380</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LR publishing problem : Can not create new albums ... Again</title>
      <description>Hello,

I've tried to update my website today and create a new album. But it's impossible. Here is the error that is returned by the plugins. Note that I can re-publish existing ones...  

Plug-in error log for plug-in at: /Volumes/Macintosh HD/Dropbox/Documents/Chris/PHOTO/PluginsLR/koken.lrplugin

**** Error 1

An error occurred while attempting to update the settings for this collection.
Saving album failed. The server did not return an error message. Contact Koken support for more help.

Koken version :  0.20.5
Plugin version :  1.2.10
LR version : 5.7

</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 18:46:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11544590</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warmup the cache</title>
      <description>Hi!
I like Koken and its embeded cache system for the images. But I’d like to know if there is (or will have) a command (or a script) to warmup the cache for all the images/resolutions and speed up the website loading.

Thanks,
Sylvain</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2015 17:50:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11541509</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Export/Import Theme Settings</title>
      <description>Hi there,

is there any possibility to export and import all the settings I did for a theme (here: Madison 2)?
For I have to port my theme to another installation and I don't want to do all the visual setup again.

Thanx for a quick answer,
Tom</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2015 11:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11540733</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wrong URL after migrate</title>
      <description>Hi koken team, 

I've migrate my website to a new server and now not under a sub-domain. Some images are always linked with the URL of the sub-domain.

You can see the problem here http://www.christophepenninckx.com/albums/hong-kong/ 

Try to share and you will see the old URL with the sub-domain : vps

What can I do to solve the problem ?

Regards, 

Chris</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 20:26:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11530616</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text below images in gallery</title>
      <description>Hi there,

I am trying to remove the date published and file name information of all my photos in the gallery. I can't figure out how to remove them and they are unnecessary/look bad, any help is greatly appreciated. 

Regards,
Matthew</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 18:29:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11529963</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pointing URL to my Koken site</title>
      <description>Hello there,

I'm rather in the dark about how to get my url samtootal.com to point to my Koken build which is sitting in the root folder of my host server.

I currently have a wordpress site attributed to the url but would like to replace this with my new shiny and amazing Koken build :-)

Please help, very excited about getting the new site live.

Many thanks,
Sam Tootal</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2015 17:16:58 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11529652</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pixelated images</title>
      <description>I am having some issues with images coming up highly pixelated.  I've cleared the image cache in the Image Publishing sections in options and tried all 3 processing options.  Two being Imagemagik and one being GD.  There always seems to be some images that are pixelated, but not all of them.  I'm using the Boulevard theme.  Is there a way to force just single images to be re-rendered?  It would make this a whole lot easier.  </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 20:39:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11527573</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problems with Lightroom 5.7</title>
      <description>Hi,

I am using Koken (updated yesterday to 0.20.5) with the newest Lr-Plugin and Lr 5.7. If I try to upload a new album, I'll get

AgExportSession:recordRemoteCollectionId: remote ID must be a number or string

but re-upload an existing album is no problem. So this error is only shown if I create new albums. Do you have any idea, how I can fix this?

Thanks!</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2015 16:33:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11526524</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Option to set the size of the images in my content feed</title>
      <description>Is there an option to set the image size of my content feed (http://zugegensein.de/feed/content/recent.rss).

I currently try to setup a MailChimp campain with this rss feed and the image within the feed is to big for an email campain.

I would like to control the image size.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2015 12:30:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11521010</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assigning cover photo to set</title>
      <description>Hello All,

I have a link on my homepage (Vehicles) that links to all the vehicle pictures I take. When clicking on that link, I  am taken to the page that has different sets listed by the car manufacturer. For example, Volvo, Audi, etc. When clicking on one of those sets, it shows the different albums for that specific manufacturer. For example when clicking on Audi, you will see albums within for A4, A5, A6, etc... I would like to know if there is any way that I can assign a cover photo for the car manufacturer sets?

Vehicles&gt;Car Manufacturer Set&gt;Model Albums
or
Vehicles&gt;Ford Set&gt;Mustang Album

How can I put a Ford Logo as a cover for the Ford Set? And I don't want it to be any picture I have from the albums within it. I guess that's the key point.

Thank you!</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 17:23:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11514726</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Display of Vertical Images on AXIS II Albums</title>
      <description>Hi there, I currently have my website running with the AXIS 2 theme and overall I am very impressed. I do however have a question in regard to the display of vertical images in the album view.

I predominately shoot panoramas with an aspect ratio of 3:1. The horizontal (vast majority of my images) images look fantastic! However the thumb nails for any vertical image look enormous in comparison to the horizontal images (this is exacerbated due to my aspect ratio of 3:1  - which means vertical images can display up to nine times the size).

Example (please refer to the vertical images at the bottom of the page): http://www.timwrate.com.au/albums/outback/

I was wondering if you were able to cap the vertical size of a thumbnail in the album view.

I think this may be possible with CSS - but I'm not that familiar with code.

Many thanks,

Tim</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 05:43:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11513268</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Album Cover Error</title>
      <description>I followed the instructions to change the album cover and even after the pop-up message claims a specific image has been made the album cover, this is not reflected in the live site. 

I am using the Ensemble theme. 

Kind Regards, 

T Barker</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 10:50:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11508012</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How do I control vertical spacing between elements?</title>
      <description>Referring to http://edbeckphotography.com/koken/pages/real-estate-photography/
Using Axis-2 theme

I'm having a problem reducing the vertical space between the headers and the paragraphs.

I've tried quite a few CSS edits, currently I'm using:

.body-left{
	text-align:left;
}
.p-nopad {
    margin-top:0em !important;
    padding-top:0em !important;
    border-top:0em !important;
    } 
.h2-nopad{
    margin-bottom:0em !important;
    padding-bottom:0em !important;
    border-bottom:0em !important;
    }

and my HTML is prefaced with


</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 13:33:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11505118</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Integrate Koken in static Website</title>
      <description>Hi there,

Sorry if this is a dumb question or if it's in the wrong category but any help is really appreciated.

I have a portfolio website already, static and hand coded, and want to incorporate koken into the two pages that display the images, rather than to move my whole site over to koken and try to incorporate it into a custom theme. I'm comfortable using the lens tags to display content but can I use them on a static page in a similar way you can use the wordpress loop? Any links to articles about incorporating koken for a gallery in a static page would be really helpful. I've done a google search and cant find anything...

cheers
Philip

</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 14:56:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11503038</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Front page not loading properly</title>
      <description>Hi, when I go to my web page (www.javanng.com) after I used Koken, I get a list of files in that directory rather than a front page - the admin panel works when I click on preview.php - but there is no public front page.  Please help!

Many Thanks

Javan

</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2015 19:12:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11501237</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remove index.php from Links</title>
      <description>I have a problem with index.php. I tried different codes with htaccess but nothing worked and the code i find for removing index.php leads to an internal error page.

I also proofed that mod rewrite is enabled and is working.

I think the htaccess files have wrong links but i dont get it to work with my directory.

My .htaccess and index.php files are in the same folder  /. Then i have koken installed in /koken
My htaccess works with this code only.

## Rewrite Rules (Pretty URLs)
## These rules remove index.php/ from your published site links
## and also speed up the serving of cached images.

	RewriteEngine On
	RewriteBase /koken
 
	# Pass images requests back to PHP if they do not exist
	RewriteCond %{REQUEST_METHOD} =GET
	RewriteCond %{REQUEST_FILENAME} !-f
	RewriteCond %{REQUEST_URI} /koken/storage/cache/images(/(([0-9]{3}/[0-9]{3})|custom)/.*)$
	RewriteRule . /koken/i.php?path=%1 [L]
 


 
## This ruleset ensures core Koken JS and CSS are cached
## for 1 year. These files are always timestamped in new releases,
## so it is safe to cache them for long periods of time.

	ExpiresActive On
	# Set default to 0 so .php/API requests are not cached
	ExpiresDefault A0
 
	# Do not cache MP4s, as Chrome and others tend to fail on first playback
	
		
			ExpiresActive Off
			Header set Cache-Control "private, no-cache, no-store, proxy-revalidate, no-transform"
			Header set Pragma "no-cache"
		
	
 
	# Console javascript and CSS is timestamped and can be aggressively cached
	
		ExpiresByType text/javascript "access plus 1 year"
		ExpiresByType application/javascript "access plus 1 year"
		ExpiresByType application/x-javascript "access plus 1 year"
		ExpiresByType text/css "access plus 1 year"
	
 
	# Cached images are timestamped and can be aggressively cached
	
		ExpiresDefault "access plus 1 year"
	

 
## End Rewrite Rules
 
############################################
#######	 END KOKEN .htaccess rules  ########
############################################

I also noticed i cant dele storage/cache/api...but i tried setting 777 and didnt work.. but i tried some things with wordpres and there are no problems set 777 to my files.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 14:42:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11493444</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>URLS</title>
      <description>Hi There,

I wondered if there is any way to not have album in the URL, for example:

http://hellomozart.co.uk/index.php?/albums/trailers/
Is it possible to have it as:
http://hellomozart.co.uk/trailers

Thanks in advance for your help,

Jason
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2015 21:40:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11489339</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madison 2 Theme - Responsive or not?</title>
      <description>I've spent the last week, on my desktop, putting together a site using the Madison theme.

The desktop monitor is big and the site looks great on it.

My problem is that, when viewed on my laptop, a scroll bar appears on the right of the screen for the Homepage image. There is only one image on the Homepage.

The site looks worse when viewed on my iPhone, when all that appears is the image - no side menu, unless I click on the icon on the top left corner.

Am I right in thinking that the Madison theme is not Responsive, in the traditional web-design sense of the term?

I would like my site to look the same across all devices. While a scroll bar on a laptop is just about acceptable, the viewing experience on a mobile phone is not. (I don't own a tablet, so I haven't had a chance to check.)

If Madison isn't Responsive, are any of the Koken themes?

You have a superb product. I hope I'm wrong in my take on its Responsiveness.

Thanks.

D.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 15:40:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11488291</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changing Twitter and Facebook name links to .gif buttons. How?</title>
      <description>I have inputted my Twitter and Facebook details via Settings/Administrator, and I have published them on my Madison site via Add Links.

I now have the words Twitter and Facebook in the left column, and if I click on them, I'm taken to my respective pages. Great.

But, I'd like them to be .gif buttons, not words.

How can I make this change?

Thanks.

D.

</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 15:50:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11483076</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madison 2 / Splash slideshow / iPad problem</title>
      <description>My new website is made with Madison 2 and it runs perfect on my iMac and iPhone 6. But I have a curious problem on my iPad air. In landscape mode the site is shown really good, no problems. But if I turn the iPad to the portrait mode, vertical I mean. the splash slideshow does not run. I only see the navigation and a spinning wheel, no pictures.

I am full of hope that someone can help me.

The url of my site: http://www.yef.info


Peter</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2015 12:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11482093</link>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
