<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>help.koken.me :: Essays and Pages</title>
    <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/topics/696985-essays-and-pages</link>
    <description>Essays and Pages articles</description>
    <item>
      <title>Balenciaga Outlet rap music</title>
      <description>The Fashion History How Urban Clothing Started? Urban clothing comes into existence on the verge of hip hop, punk and Balenciaga Outlet rap music in 1970s in New York. The link between music and urban clothing prompt the rise of clothing companies; even some of the hip hop artists have created too their own clothing lines.
The followers of urban clothing were more amplified when their favorite artists started wearing baggy shirts and Urban wear became viral and reached other countries such as Australia, London and even Japan.
Along the street style, urban wear is considered as one of the trendiest style most young people would prefer. It expresses selfhood and savoirfaire. Especially men, they love urban style clothing as there can be a lot of designs and options to choose from.
Clothing designer companies have been offering unique and exclusive items. They guarantee that there will be nobody wearing tees on the same design. Balenciaga Bag Clothing designers warrant not only style, so too comfort. Urban clothing seems to be very cool to wear.
Anyone who clothed himself is extremely appealing and depicts an air of confidence. Through urban clothing, gangsters begin to develop, where people all draw on oversized clothing and converse sneakers. What Marks Urban Style and Clothing? Urban clothing is more than a hip hop style. The accessories and all the diamond necklaces are symbols of wealth and prestige.
Aside from oversized clothings and large accessories, the shirts of urban clothing are usually dark; and designed with Balenciaga Handbags peculiar, erratic images such as skulls. Urban clothing can be leather jackets, denim pants, slacks, statement tees, athletic jerseys, hoodies and accessories like belts, watch and bracelets.
http://www.valentinoshoesa.com/valentino-boots-c-9/
http://yoamoabarranquilla.com/profiles/blogs/valentino-shoes-sale-walk-to-town
http://www.lhbon.com/mulberry-men-bags-c-201_202/
http://shosovavere.yolasite.com/
https://www.minds.com/blog/view/485338759588487168/valentino-sneakers-eye-who-we</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 13:22:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14287814</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text on home page</title>
      <description>Hi,

Sorry to ask as this seems like it should be so simple but how do you add some introduction copy/text to the 'Home' page of the Elementary Theme so that it sits under the navigation and above the 'Home' page featured image/slideshow??

This would really help me and so many thanks.

Jason (London)
PS. Just installed Koken today and it is amazing. Shocked that you guys want to move on to other things as this is awesome. As soon as somone new takes over I'll be buying Themes and all the plugins I need.

</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 10:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14259799</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>balenciaga handbag observation</title>
      <description>Accomplishments of Queen Elizabeth II

Princess Elizabeth Alexandra Mary is the queen of 16 independent states, which are known as the Commonwealth realms. She was born in London on 21st April 1926, declared as the queen at the age of 25, and has reigned for more than five decades of enormous social change and development. Queen Elizabeth II was the first child of the Duke and Duchess of York, who subsequently became King [b][url=http://www.lhbon.com/balenciaga-c-3/]balenciaga handbag[/url][/b] George VI and Queen Elizabeth.

By the age of 12, she distinguished herself as a gifted and eager horsewoman. At an early age of 14, with the breaking of World War II she made her first radio broadcast, reassuring the safety of orphaned children. Although she was born and brought up in a royal family, her parents were determined that Elizabeth should neither be shielded nor spoiled. On 20th November 1947, she got married to Philip, who was the Duke of Edinburgh and her third cousin through queen Victoria. It [b][url=http://www.lhbon.com/balenciaga-c-3/]balenciaga bag sale[/url][/b] was the perfect blend of her sense of regal duty and a love of simple pleasures, which uniquely characterized the royalty and integrity of her reign.

From all the daunting experiences she had during her reign, Queen Elizabeth II understood the tautology of Shakespeare's observation, which states, "Uneasy lies the head that wears a crown". Some of her major accomplishments are as follows:

the end of the second world war, princess Elizabeth traveled extensively to attend public functions throughout the British Isles. These visits included attending the launch of a new aircraft carrier in Belfast, a tour of Ulster in March 1946, and attending the National Eisteddfod of Wales in August 1946.

1957, the Queen on her official visit to the United States, became the first monarch to open the nation's Parliament.

Elizabeth II has constantly been an integral part of the ongoing transformation of the old British empire into the new British Commonwealth, and its modern successor (the Commonwealth of Nations). She acts as the host to the Heads of States of the Commonwealth realms. She holds Investitures in Britain and other Commonwealth countries, at which she presents honors to people who have distinguished themselves in public life.

she was declared a queen, she succeeded her father as ColonelinChief of all the Guards Regiments and the Corps of Royal Engineers, and as CaptainGeneral of the Royal Regiment of [b][url=http://www.lhbon.com/balenciaga-c-3/]Balenciaga Bag[/url][/b] Artillery.

her reign, Elizabeth has also demonstrated support for interfaith relations and has rendered respect for all the religions.

important of all, she has achieved an excellent reputation as a good and wise ruler, and is truly loved and respected by her people.

common practice, Queen Elizabeth II is referred to as "The Queen or Her Majesty", and in the year 2002, she celebrated 50 years of her reign.

2012, the Queen celebrated her 'diamond jubilee' on completion of her 60 years of sovereignty.

Despite the controversies and scandals surrounding her children and other members of the royal family, and the sad demise of princess Diana, she still remains the respected head of the state.

http://www.cellphonecasesa.com/oakley-galaxy-s4-cases-c-84_91/
http://www.cellphonecasesa.com/louis-vuitton-galaxy-s4-cases-c-84_93/
http://www.cellphonecasesa.com/iphone-6-plus-cases-c-82/
http://www.airjordanmvp.com/air-jordan-11-retro-7210-378037002-p-535.html
http://www.lhbon.com/women-wallets-c-122_128/
http://www.lhbon.com/giuseppe-zanotti-c-48/
http://www.lhbon.com/celine-box-c-13_15/</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 06:37:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13595294</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mangement research papaers writing service</title>
      <description>The management research papers should be having the tips and ideas about the make the perfect management in their organization. The writers can be collect some of the important points and ideas about organization management and provides in their writing paper. The research papers about the management is must taking the basic problems and innovative ideas about making perfect management.The excellent essay reviews writing service is build the some more types of research writing papers.


https://reviews.clazwork.com</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 10:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13086078</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple Essay Pages</title>
      <description>Wondering if it's possible to make two different essay pages? I want to be able to blog on two categories and keep them in separate feeds...</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 21:44:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13065349</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to publish an essay?</title>
      <description>I have created an essay with a title and gave publish live. But, later I couldn't find any such essays. It shows as 0 items. How can I retrieve the work? or How can I do it without error? </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 14:57:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13051520</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dates on Essay grid</title>
      <description>Hi there - I just wanted to know if it's possible to have the dates of the essays show up on the essay grid - as I want to use it as a blog, it'd be very helpful for the dates to show up.  I'm using Regale 2 as my theme.  Thanks for your help.

Best wishes,

Joseph</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 15:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13039678</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Magnific Popup iFrame</title>
      <description>Hello all,

Is it possible to use this function "Magnific Popup" http://dimsemenov.com/plugins/magnific-popup/  for iFrame?
I would like to click on a small preview picture an then open a magnific popup iFrame with the interactiv panorama. These Panos are integrated by small iFrame in an essay site and look not so god  
here is my pano site example: http://xinside.de/koken/app/site/site.php?url=/pages/panorama/</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 01:12:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12880467</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigation</title>
      <description>Hi,
is it possible or can I insert an album to the page without a preview image in the main content area?
It would be great, if it would be possible to have access to an album only via the navigation bar (to clean things up a little)
Thanks for your help!

Regards,
Manfred</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 08:20:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12831472</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>inclusion of php code</title>
      <description>Hello everybody,

I am quite new to Koken and I am sorry to ask again if this question has already been answered.

How can I add a small php script in the middle of my page. My purpose is quite simple, I have a (working) php script that lists the files in a  subdirectory of my website and display a table of links to them and I need to move this little script in a koken page.

Regards.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 17:51:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12767209</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problem writing Essay</title>
      <description>Last night i made an Essay. When i entered the title it was Really slow creating the essay itself. 
But it was created after a few minutes. I entered the text i wanted to enter, uploaded a photo with it. Pushed the publish it button, And everything looked normal. But......
When i look into the news area of the website the essay is not sowing... When i take a look at the draft area it looks like only the Essay title has been created. When i try to deleted it from the drafts it still stays in the draft area.. i cannot do anything with it.. Also when i try to create another essay it does the same.. Only the title is created in the draft area.. and you cannot do anything with it.. Already cleared the system cache.. But everything seems normal.. What do i have to do to fix this...
Please help... </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 May 2015 15:02:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12745349</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change picture size in page or essays</title>
      <description>Hi,

I read the post about image sizing (http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/articles/1078046-image-loading-and-formatting) and I do not find this structure in the Madison 2 theme.

the structure in Madison 2 is like "[koken_photo label="Maroc-195.jpg" id="725" size="" media_type="image" link="album" album="16" caption="none"]" 

how is it then possible to specify a height and width in this case?  by simply adding something like width="600" height="400"?  Nothing seems to change, so I wonder how the container is defined in this case and how I would be able to specify the container size.

Thank you in advance for your answer</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 16:05:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12666646</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>a spa christian louboutin shoes on sale is a fulltime </title>
      <description>You have a flare for beauty. You love making people feel pampered and relaxed through beauty and spa treatments. Opening a spa business is [b][url=http://www.hjbon.com/louboutin-daffodile-c-1_65/]christian louboutin daffodile pumps[/url][/b] your dream but you have no idea how to get started. You have your concept in place. You know what services you are going to offer. You even know where you would like to open your [b][url=http://www.hjbon.com/louboutin-flats-c-1_66/]christian louboutin flats[/url][/b]spa business. in 2009, which was a slight decline of 3.2 percent from previous years. That seems like a lot of competition considering that over the past decade the number of spa locations has grown from 5,700 in 1999. 

Just like any other business, a spa is a fulltime commitment. It takes more than just services, products and themes. Opening a spa requires licenses, employees, inspections and a multitude of other needs to be effective and profitable. Spa Industry reported that 143 million people visited a spa in 2009, despite being down 10.2 percent in previous years. The decline in revenue is 4.3 percent or $12.3 billion in 2009. [b][url=http://www.hjbon.com/louboutin-heels-c-1_67/]christian louboutin heels for sale[/url][/b] These declines may be due to market saturation and overlapping concepts, themes or other similar product/service offerings. 

Does this mean you have to stop your dreams of owning a spa? No. This simply means that there is a market of willing consumers looking for the next great spa, rather than just the next spa. The spa industry has grown in revenue 7.3 billion over the past decade and in popularity with more than 50 million spa visits. There are options when looking to opening your own spa business: [b][url=http://www.hjbon.com/louboutin-pumps-c-1_3/]christian louboutin pumps on sale[/url][/b] 

Don't enter into a saturated market. Many business owners, not just spa owners, enter into a market that is already saturated, meaning there are similar businesses within a 510 mile radius. In this [b][url=http://www.hjbon.com/louboutin-pigalle-c-1_4/]christian louboutin pigalle[/url][/b] situation businesses will be competing for the same customers, employees and dollars. When you start your research always check within close proximity of your targeted location. 

Decide if you want to lease or build your [b][url=http://www.hjbon.com/christian-louboutin-c-1/]christian louboutin shoes on sale[/url][/b] building and equipment. Leasing vs. buying is always one of the hardest decisions to make when you are starting a business. Entrepreneur suggests asking yourself these questions: How long do you plan to keep the asset? Is a new or used building the best fit for your needs? How frequently does technology change with this asset? What are your financing options for purchasing vs. leasing? What are the tax [b][url=http://www.hjbon.com/christian-louboutin-c-1/]christian louboutin outlet[/url][/b]benefits of buying vs. leasing? 

Establish strong products and services. A strong product and [b][url=http://www.hjbon.com/christian-louboutin-c-1/]cheap christian louboutin shoes[/url][/b] service offering is the key to capturing your target audience. To effectively price your spa services, you need to shop your competitors as well [b][url=http://www.hjbon.com/louboutin-peep-toe-c-1_2/]christian louboutin peep toe shoes[/url][/b]as do research to ensure you are priced competitively to other salons in your city. Also be willing to change the services and products of your spa to stay uptodate within the industry. 

http://www.airjordanon.com/air-jordan-14-c-78/
http://www.celinehandbagse.com/celine-small-belt-c-77/
http://www.hjbon.com/balenciaga-giant-12-c-41_49/
http://www.limitedbeatsbydre.com/beats-by-dre-studio-c-24/
http://www.hjbon.com/giuseppe-zanotti-pumps-c-262_263/
http://www.hjbon.com/beats-by-dre-pro-c-68_102/
http://www.airjordanon.com/air-jordan-3-c-66/
http://www.balenciagatop.com/balenciag-first-c-2/</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 16:23:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12624581</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text layout</title>
      <description>The text placed above my photo stories (albums) takes a form oa a column on the left side and I would like it to stretch across the page, covering the length of the four photos. I can't figure out how to manage it.
Thanks</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 May 2015 08:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12517474</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>File name in Blog Posts</title>
      <description>Hello, 

Could you please implant the option to uncheck to show the image title in pictures, which are in Blog posts. Or would it be possible to add a separate "alt" field globally to every picture, so you can leave the title flied empty but in the alt-field you can give a description for SEO. 

Thanks. 
Kind regards, Sebastian </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 18:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12364206</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>usage of unpublished or private images in essays or pages</title>
      <description>Hi,

I would like to be able to use images in pages or essays, without having to use a public album that has to contain all those images and as such is visible to all.

For instance I would like a contact form to be used with a picture of me on the right or left hand side, but I do not want this picture to be seen in any of the public album.
How can I do something like this?

Publishing floating images is easy to do with a plugin found on internet.

Thank you for your answers</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 21:30:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12310705</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Paginated pages not rendering</title>
      <description>I've been running a custom theme for some time now and I'm just getting around to implementing the essays section. 

So far everything is working fine except for pagination. The links display properly, and if I inspect them it appears as though Koken is writing out the proper pagination links, but when I click any of them I get taken to a blank page. 

I'm not getting a 404, so it seems like Koken is finding the right link, but it's failing to render anything.

For instance, on my essays page (www.benoitdesigninc.com/essays/), I have the amount loaded limited to 2. There are 5 essays total, so I get three page links at the bottom of my list (4 if you count the "&gt;" link).

The code generated for the links is:


		1

		2

		3

		&amp;gt;
	


This looks like it should work, but any of the links just load up a blank page. When I click on "2", for instance, I'm taken to:

	http://www.benoitdesigninc.com/essays/page/2/

which is empty. Upon inspection, it looks as though the  tag is being filled in, but the  tag is left completely blank.

I've deleted cache, republished the site, all to no avail.

Any thoughts?

-Nick Benoit
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 22:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12247064</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essays are empty</title>
      <description>Some of my essays are not showing. The page is there, and there is a title and a comments section, but nothing in-between. And I cannot seem to see any commonality with the essays that don't show.

Here is one that doesn't show: http://colouringinteam.co.uk/portfolio/essays/2015/05/understanding-legibility/

And here is one that does: http://colouringinteam.co.uk/portfolio/essays/2014/06/redesigning-national-rail-tickets/

Please help - I really don't have a clue how to fix this. I've installed the latest update,and cleared the cache.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 14:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12216627</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Insert Slideshot with a unlistenend Album</title>
      <description>Hi

I want to use the Slideshow with only a unlisted Album. I think this interesting for all who want to show some pictures only in the slideshow, but not in the galerie as an album. 

Can you please the build it that we can also use unlisted albums for the Slideshow?</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 20:58:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12172345</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact form question.</title>
      <description>Hi guys,
Loving the contact form, can finally throw away the google doc as a result.

Quick question though. I'm using the Chastain theme, black background, white foreground. The form works perfectly, however the success text is black, and I can't seem to find an option to change it to white. 

The form is here: http://shaunneary.com/index.php?/pages/contact-1/

You can highlight it and it'll read "Thank you for contacting shaunneary.com".

It's only a minor quibble, but I'm just wondering if there is a way for this to be made visible?
Thanks in advance,
Shaun</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2015 15:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12152464</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problem with latin signs in text editor</title>
      <description>Hello!
Every time i try to write "Å‚" (alt + l)text editor automatically switches to upper index mode (like, in math, 2^3).

Is there any way disable this key-combination,  to install different text editor OR disable it and make it a pure-html text? 

cheers,
Peter</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 14:51:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11695502</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slug Editing and Re-Editing While in Essay Model</title>
      <description>Hi Todd, Brad, and Lauren,

As always, you know me, I have been with Koken since DAY ONE of private testing and I have stick to it. I'm glad to experience the product's growth and functionality. I have nothing but highest praise and commendations to your team. Please consider the following request for improvement of Koken: the ability to edit and re-edit slugs in Essay mode. Unless I overlooked something, the slugs could only be redacted once the essay or page gets published.

Let's try a real world, practical example of how I use Koken and cross post to my Twitter via the Buffer App and IFTTT.

Let's now suppose that I'm writing an essay exactly titled, "How to Use Koken (@Koken) to Publish Your Photography Website." In the current version of Koken, the Text Model will create the following slug "how-to-use-koken-koken-to-publish-your-photography-website."

BUT!!!

I don't want the repeated "koken-koken" in the slug! If I want to edit the slug, I can't. I'd have to publish the essay and then head back into draft mode to be able to edit the link.

Right?

Then...I'd have to update the slug and finally hit the Update at the bottom right for the changes to be live on the site.

WHY THE SUGGESTION?

Currently, Koken has no way to auto-post to social media, e.g. Twitter. I'd have to use its RSS + IFFF + BufferApp. Even if people don't use Koken RSS the way I do, I thinkÃ¢â‚¬â€being able to edit and re-edit the slug while writing the Essay is efficient and workflow-enhancing.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 22:23:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11676334</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>iframes in pages</title>
      <description>I need to insert a google calendar into a page. However the iFrame does not play nicely. When I want a 700 px tall iFrame, Koken displays a tiny calendar, even adjusting the size of the attributes in the iFrame set up from the google calendar fails.
Any suggestions.?
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 01:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11664934</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>e-mail form (Needs a loader)</title>
      <description>Hi guys,

thanks for implementing the e-mail form into Koken, really like it.
There needs to be a loader to indicate something is happening after clicking the send button. Because when you press it, you don't know something is happening or not.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 16:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11652564</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>embedding email link</title>
      <description>trying to embed a link to my email while writing a new page. I don't want to use the contact form, but can't seem to find a way to make a link to send an email.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 14:02:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11651929</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>linking between pages</title>
      <description>Hi,
I would like to know when you're going to add links between pages... could be very convenient!

thanks,m.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 08:07:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11650074</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Password protected essays</title>
      <description>Hello again

Are there any plans to implement password protection for essays?
Thanks

Andi</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2015 15:41:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11640259</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If I add a contact form the text input does not show</title>
      <description>If I add a contact form to my page, very handy! It does work but the text input does not show while you type in the box..

See my site.. http://ewoudkoster.nl/pages/contact-info/

Any idea how I can fix this? Can I change the font colour for the form?

Tnx for your time!

Kind regards,

Ewoud</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2015 09:12:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11617588</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Changing Size of Blog Title in Axis 2</title>
      <description>Hi,

I was wondering if there was any way to change the size of blog titles in Axis 2?

I know there are options to change the letter spacing etc, but can't see an option for the text size itself.

Thanks!</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Apr 2015 16:21:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11579552</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Size of the Font from the Date</title>
      <description>Hello

Look at this Screenshot: http://666kb.com/i/cxf2twr780cqnpc6q.jpg

The Size of the Font from the Date ist to small. How can i make it bigger?

I use the Axis Theme</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 22:53:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11579486</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>text on homepage</title>
      <description>Dear Koken friends,

First of all: thank you koken for the contactpage...its great!!

My question is: How can I get some introduction text on my homepage? When I use the default homepage, the only thing I can put on the page is some image I assign in the library. But I want text instead of an other image. Please help.

greeting
Momo</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 21:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11578136</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Published date in essays</title>
      <description>Hi Koken Team!
I'm using Repertoire theme and have some essays for which I've changed the template setting to NOT show the published date. This works for the home page left frame, where my featured essays are listed. But if I'm on the single essay page in the bottom navigation (arrows + preview of prior or next essay) it shows the published date nevertheless.
As a wokaround I tried to delete the published date from the properties of the essay page but it's added again  automatically right after.
Could you please have a look on this? Thank you!

Kind regards,
Carsten</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Apr 2015 08:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11576369</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image Placement and Grouping (Tiling) Options</title>
      <description>Hi Todd, Brad, and Lauren,

I was wondering, if the following feature for images tiling is in the works. Suppose I upload three images in the following ratios:

(1) 3:2
(2) 3:4

In the current Koken Page, the image uploads will be added in a top down format, without any visual rearrangement.

Ideally and for the visually-pleasing and most effect use to screen real estate, is grouping or tiling in the works? Such that the landscaped 3:2 will appear at the top (or bottom) AND the two 3:4 images will be positioned adjacently top/bottom?

What if the user uploaded (3) 3:4 images? This grid/tiling option will make those three images displayed like a triptych for visual presentation and screen real estate.

Thank you for your time and consideration.

Best in health and warmest wishes,

Ronald</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 01:32:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11573569</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>new email contact form / layout problem</title>
      <description>Hi!

When using white background color together with madison scheme - the new email contact form will not bei displayed properly!
You cannot see the text fileds and the send button (all borders of fields are invisible...)

Please correct!

Thanks / Georg</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Apr 2015 08:20:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11571543</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preview Draft</title>
      <description>Hi, I'm brand new, hoping to have my site to go live within the next week.  

Chris Rault (Co-founder of HeadwayRocket and a huge fan of yours) is my web designer, and has been working on this for months now. We've finally reached the point where I can begin testing publishing.  

I have searched and searched and cannot find where/how to preview an essay before publishing. I can't publish blind, of course. But I can't for the life of me find how to do this, either in your manuals or these forums. Or by using the program.  The "Site/Link/View" feature appears to do the exact same thing the "Site/Link/Copy" feature does - it simply copies the link to the clipboard. But the link returns an error.  The "Inspector" feature also returns an error.  Chris is not available today, to get help from him on this, so I'm hoping someone there might be able to enlighten me. I'm sure I'm missing some huge obvious button somewhere and I've embarrassed myself here.

Thanks, look forward to your help.

Liza May</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2015 08:28:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11570386</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text markup options for curriculums</title>
      <description>Hi!

I was wondering if you guys have thought about implementing some text markup options voor curriculums.
Like making it possible to create margins or columns of text.

It can be something simple, like this for instance:
http://www.geertgoiris.info/content/index.php?s=cv

I'm kind of missing the option to organise my curriculum with koken for the moment.

Thanks!</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2015 13:38:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11569469</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to re-order images once inserted in an essay?</title>
      <description>How to re-order inserted images in a essay?

Is this possible? Because i've tried everything!

Thank you!

Paul

</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2015 19:29:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11568029</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>text</title>
      <description>Hello! Please help me to understend how to write a blog. I can't do it</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 14:58:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11567378</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change the colors of the contact form</title>
      <description>Hi Guys,

Great job on the contact form ! Really what i wanted. 
The only thing i couldn't do is change the colors of the Send button (it is almost not visible when you use the dark theme) and change the colors of the fields where to enter text (this is now the same color as the background.. So you can almost not see it) 
For an example you can take a look at my contact page.
http://www.maestro-photography.nl/pages/contact-form/

Hope you can help me with it. 

Best Regards,

Bas</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2015 16:57:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11561595</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2 columns for Page or Essay with Boulevard theme</title>
      <description>Hi! I have a question,  does anybody know how I can have 2 columns for an "about" page for example? Is it possible to make it? 

Thank you a lot!!</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2015 08:10:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11560540</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>new contact form pages</title>
      <description>Hi

I've added a new contact form to my site, however on the button to send email, the text is white, on a white button, how can I change this?

Thanks

</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 14:47:37 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11552559</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Captcha in Contact Form</title>
      <description>Hello

Thank you for puplish a contact form for korken!!! :)

How does it look there with the hedging against spam? Will there soon be a way for Captcha give?</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 21:19:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11552105</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Contact Form Center Request</title>
      <description>Hi Todd, Brad, and Lauren,

It is safe to say that I'd like to exclaim, "THANK YOU!!!" for the new contact form. Although I have no need for the form, I acknowledge the benefit of the newly released contact form for other Koken users.

Which brings me to a consideration: how do you feel about the centering the contact form fields? In its current release, it's left aligned. Unless I have overlooked the ability to center the fields via Custom CSS...will you please consider an option for the contact fields to be centered and right aligned?

Thank you for your time. I have been an early adopter of Koken since it's private beta days. I've glad to to be using and helping test Koken.

Best in health and warmest wishes,

Ron</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2015 19:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11548956</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Space between Title / Divider Line / Content</title>
      <description>Hello,

i am really struggeling with adjusting the layout of the custom pages so they match my blog and photo pages. The blog and album have the same space between title / divider line / content. I want that my custom pages look the same but there is more space between those things so the layout bumps around when i am browsing the site. I can adjust the width of the content but how can i adjust the height of the spaces? I tried it with some custom css but it seems that i can't get it right.

Any help would be deeply appreciated. I really love the layout of Axis 2 but this issue is really annoying me. Please help. :-)

Kind regards,
Daniel</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2015 21:53:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11545167</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No titles + captions with library photo</title>
      <description>I insert library photos on a page and edit them to show the title or caption of their album but nothing is shown. Not sure but might happen since last update of Image Protector. On photos inserted before that update the titles are shown.
Can you check, please?</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2015 22:42:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11534784</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Images no longer showing in essays, sized at 1px x 1px</title>
      <description>I have published essays in the past inserting images below &amp; between text and it worked fine (see http://morgenschulerphotography.com/index.php?/essays/abandoned-country/) but now every time i try posting an essay with inserted images nothing shows when I view the post live on my site (I double checked that the actual code looks exactly the same in the working blog post as in the non-working one) see: http://morgenschulerphotography.com/index.php?/essays/photolush/

I looked at the code in the Chrome Developer tool and it says the size of the image is set to "tiny" and it is only 1px x 1px. Did I change a setting that causes this o is something broken? Here's the img code for one of the images: 

</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 14:54:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11525459</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>API for Desk...</title>
      <description>I am really interested in starting to use koken as a replacement for my blog. I would really like to use desk (htps://desk.pm)) with the essay section and I know the author would support it, if there was an API for the essay and pages section.

Would be awesome to get that API published so we can start using 3rd party apps!

Thanks</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 08:19:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11518784</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dublicated images in essays</title>
      <description>Hi ,

after one of the last updates started to get duplicated images in esseys , even as in markup there is only one 

removing the image from text , just gets previous one duplicated 

( essay contain both images from album and directly inserted - so maybe some count is broken because of this ? )

example :
2 images at the end , ( 2nd and 3rd from the end )
http://travelogue.photography/stories/gibraltar/</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 00:47:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11511107</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacing between blog posts</title>
      <description>Hi all

Is there a solution to get a little bit more space between two different blog posts? I'm using Madison 2, and for the moment, spacing between title and image of post #1 is the same as spacing between image #1 and title of post #2. So it's not quite clear whether an image belongs to the title above or below.
Maybe there's a css snippet to achieve some separation?

Thanks in advance

Andi</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 16:14:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11499445</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slideshow in essay not using the right cover image</title>
      <description>Hi there,

I wanted to post a link of an essay (http://www.bernardpanier.be/essays/2015/03/blue/) in a FB post and noticed the image suggested is one of another album.

Since the album is hidden I initially used a public album and them changed the ID in the HTML code. The wrong cover image is that of the initial album.

I cleared cache in the hope this would resolve it but it didn't. Any suggestion on how to solve this.

Theme is Boulevard.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2015 15:01:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11498860</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No linking from one page to another</title>
      <description>I want to create a link within a page to another page but when marking text to add a link and choose "Link to site content" it offers me only albums. So to achieve this I have to open the target page live in browser and copy and paste the URL as external link URL into "Insert link".
Why are no essays or pages offered for linking? </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2015 17:31:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11497947</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mosaic in essay</title>
      <description>I read through a lot of questions and answers posted and I understood that there is no way to display images in an essay as mosaics, is this still the most current status? I would love to see this feature soon!

Thx
Stefan</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 18:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11483442</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Right- or Left-align images with text?</title>
      <description>Has the plugin at http://www.brisoft.de/en/insert-images-essays-posts/ been removed? No response from server. 

Any current advice on Right- or Left-align images with text?

Thx.</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 14:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11473733</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essays and headlines</title>
      <description>The Essays , how can I  get it to show only headlines?</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Feb 2015 21:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11466055</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Photos in text page load wrong album page</title>
      <description>Hi guys,
as well Koken is as a CMS, sometimes it drives me crazy :-). What I'm doing is: create a new page under Text, insert several library photos, one in a line, each to load the corresponding album page. That works for the first (3?) lines, from then it loads the previous photo album and once it has started this behaviour all photos load wrong albums.
I tried several times to correct it - no way - it stays weird, I deleted and recreated the page and run into the same problem again.
I'm on Koken 20.3 with Repertoire theme. Please help. Thanks!
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 16:24:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11456229</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Download entire album</title>
      <description>Love your work. I've enjoyed seeing this CMS get better and better. I would like to know if full album downloads is something that we will be able to enjoy sooner rather than later. This would allow my clients (and I'm sure many other people's clients) to stay on my website for everything rather than me directing them to something like picsurge.com or pixieset. This seems like a good next step after implementing password protection on albums.

Thanks again for all the great stuff you guys are doing. You've had a few recommendations from me :)</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2015 16:17:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11444620</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essays published date</title>
      <description>Hi, 

I tried to edit essays published time to 17:50 or 5:50 pm but i can't do that. It always modifies that to 5:50 am. I have the latest version 0.20.1 installed.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 16:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11416480</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Youtube iFrame Code in Madison Essay Page / HTML</title>
      <description>Hi,

I want to add a youtube video to my madison essay page. Size ist 320 x 240 px and it should not be resized to the whole with of the column. So I tried to insert the youtube iframe code into the html-window. Perfect result! But unfortunately the video is placed in the middle of the row, is centered. I would like to have it alined left. Is it possible? What can I do?

Thanks for your Help
Peter</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 14:41:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11416188</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Images orderin in essays</title>
      <description>Hello. 
It would be great if you can rearrange the order of images in essays. So for example to take the last to the first or add text in between two images. 
Right now I cannot change the order or add a paragraph, when I have multiple images in one blog post. 

Thanks :) </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 14:57:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11411906</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to link to a specific image page</title>
      <description>In essay or page, is there a way to link to a specific image page? I only see option to link to an album. Obviously could use HTML link but not convenient.

Thank you.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Feb 2015 08:38:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11410868</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Show featured esays with thumbnails in custom page</title>
      <description>I am using Elementary 1.5.7. On home (index) page, I display slideshow and hide featured albums and essays.

I would like to have another page display only featured essays with thumbnails as on home page. Copied index.lens to a custompage.lens and modified it to include just the header,  section, and footer. 

Quickly discovered that turning on/off the featured items on index page disables them for both pages so tried to modify the info.json page to change scope based on http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/articles/828692-settings, but can't seem to get it right. I think I'm not understanding a step because slideshow and featured essay checkboxes on custom page seem to have no effect at all.

I'm wondering if I need to change the info.json file if I don't need user input on the settings?


Tried:
"index_show_slideshow": {
	"label": "Show slideshow",
	"type": "boolean",
	"value": {
		"index": true,
		"custompage": false,
	},
	"control_first": true,
	"scope": [ "index", "custompage" ],
"scoped_values": true
},
...
"index_show_featured_essays": {
	"label": "Show featured essays",
	"type": "boolean",
	"value": {
		"index": true,
		"custompage": true
	},					
	"control_first": true,
	"scope": [ "index", "custompage" ],
	"scoped_values": true
},

 
Thank you for any help.
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Feb 2015 17:40:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11408310</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ecritures</title>
      <description>Bonjour,
comment gérer l'interlignage?
exemple: http://lauresamama.com/albums/le-jour-se-leve-encore/  Le texte est trop écarté car je dois sauter une ligne, sinon la mise à la ligne ne se fait pas et tout le texte apparaît en continu
Comment modifier le choix des typo pour mettre de l'italique par exemple?
merci beaucoup,
cordialement
Laure Samama</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Feb 2015 10:00:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11372550</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Viewing Permissions and Multiple Users</title>
      <description>I know that multiple users have been asked for already, but I wanted to get an update about this. Is there going to be any kind of multiple user interface any time soon?

I wouldn't mind contributing to the coding process, or paying some money for this feature.

What I'm looking for at the moment is any kind of rudimentary setup in order to filter out albums based on user so that I can post pictures for friends and family and they would only see content relevant to them.

I would even be willing to pay for a quick and dirty feature fork that I have to merge into future updates and enter the users and permissions in the db manually. Even if it's something as simple as creating a small table, koken_permissions_view(id, user_id, album_id) and filtering out the results for the albums view with an  inner join koken_permissions_view pv on pv.album_id=a.album_id and pv.user_id=@current_user_id

I sometimes think I'll just write my own site. I have a foundation that I started from my senior project in college, but you guys already have a highly professional system here with some awesome Lightroom integration. It's only missing multiple users and security roles.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Feb 2015 21:55:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11359057</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>front page</title>
      <description>Hello,

I would go back to the original image ( non-personalized ) of the site ( when it is appropriate to enter their email and password) . I customized this page reminds me how and I would return to the default image. What is manipulation?

Thank you</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 16:06:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11348759</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>insert a picture und a text</title>
      <description>Hi,

I have a problem inserting a small image under the text of my about-page. The image has a size of 150 x 150 px. After the import there is a broad gray box on the right side. What can I do to prevent this? In the meantime, I've used a little trick. I added a white Area beside the pic. It has now a with of 810 px. It’s the with of the text above it. But I think this is not the solution.

Here is the url of the page: http://pfey.de/koken/pages/about/
Thanks for your help

Peter</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Feb 2015 14:24:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11337359</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>design of thumbnail in essay</title>
      <description> i like to design essays like a blog. the read more is quite helpful, but i like to show a featured image in the essays overview for each essay/blog post. If i am coding it like this:














It displays all featured images in one row before the actual posts. I like to position them each right infront of their essay like

pic thumbnail title essay

begin essay

read more...

next

pic thumbnail title essay

begin essay</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2015 11:49:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11332591</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pages and sub-pages / Seiten und Unterseiten</title>
      <description>Hello,
please excuse my bad (google) English.
I would like to publish on my site several texts (Pages, no essays) and would need to the ability to create subpages. Two levels would reach me already ;) , so Home&gt; sub-page. In the navigation then the link to the main page should be, and if you click on the sub-pages should be displayed.
Alternatively, you could add a link to the bases on the main page, too, but unfortunately is displayed in the "Insert Link&gt; Link to Site Content" only the albums and not existent pages.
Is it possible that to fruition with Koken and if so how?
Thanks for the feedback.
Axel

Hallo,
bitte entschuldigen sie mein schlechtes (google) englisch.
Ich würde auf meiner Seite gerne mehrere Texte (Pages, keine Essays) veröffentlichen und bräuchte dazu die Möglichkeit, Unterseiten anzulegen. Zwei Ebenen würden mir ja schon reichen ;), also Hauptseite &gt; Unterseite. In der Navigation sollte dann der Link zur Hauptseite stehen, und wenn man dann darauf klickt, sollten die Unterseiten angezeigt werden. 
Alternativ könnte man ja auch auf der Hauptseite einen Link zu den Unterseiten einfügen, allerdings wird bei "Insert Link &gt; Link to Site Content" leider nur die Alben angezeigt und nicht vorhandene Seiten.
Gibt es die Möglichkeit, dass mit Koken umzusetzten und wenn ja wie?
Danke für die Rückmeldung.
Axel
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 23:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11316271</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bigger pictures on click in essays?</title>
      <description>Hello

In essays, the pictures have online the same size. I want to click on the image to see it in a bigger size like in the gallery, but i does not work. Here an example:

http://www.linsenschuss.de/blog/2014/10/cnc-maschinen-als-fotomodels/

I want to click on the pictures to load the bigger size. What do I have to activate it?

Thanks!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 23:03:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11316133</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>newsletter mail chimp</title>
      <description>hi,

i want to integrate a mailchimp-form to subscribe my newsletter.
i do get a code from mail chimp but i don`t know were to put it on koken..

something like this. i tried copy/paste in pages, but it did`t work..

can you help?

thanks!!!!

``



	#mc_embed_signup{background:#fff; clear:left; font:14px Helvetica,Arial,sans-serif; }
	/* Add your own MailChimp form style overrides in your site stylesheet or in this style block.
	``</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jan 2015 10:49:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11313411</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Import from Tumblr</title>
      <description>I've got a load of short posts on a Tumblr blog (just text and link) that I'd like to import to Koken. What's the easiest way to do that?</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 15:59:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11313291</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>juliademarque.com Problems</title>
      <description>Hello, I need some help. 
I'm trying to upload photos to a blog post, and when I upload them into the post the images gets out of the right order. How can I fix it? When I go inside the post album, they are in the right order.  

And, besides this, my website is not showing photos of some portfolio gallery (even though they're there). 
You can try going to "portfolio&gt;Casamentos" and "portfolio&gt;Casais", and you see no photo. But when you go there by the koken admin viewer the photos are there.  :(((

Another problem is that the emails that I send from my contact (contato) page does not arive to my email. 

I'm looking foward for your help. 
Thanks
Julia
 
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2015 18:46:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11305571</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>"Save As Draft" deletes page</title>
      <description>Saving a page as draft deletes the page completely from admin. When I then try to create the page again, it changes the slug, adding a number to it, and when I try to edit it back to the original slug I get the error: "This URL slug is already in use. Please enter a different value." So I just go with the slug it generated, write some test words and click Save As Draft again, and the new page also disappears.

I've tried clearing the system and image caches in admin, going into ftp to manually clear the /storage/cache/api and /storage/cache/site folders as well as my browser cache. The problem persists. I'm running the latest version of Koken with no updates available to me at this time.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 07:45:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11288817</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>edit page</title>
      <description>Hello dear Support Team,
I want to change something about my CV and I cannot when I go to TEXT and then PAGES I cannot even open the page to edit it.
Can you help me please?</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jan 2015 17:52:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/10759726</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>essay archive menu</title>
      <description>Hi
I have an essay archive menu in my blog with koken:dates, koken:tags and koken:categories all of which are working. I also want to have a 'recent posts' section showing the last 10 posts. I have cobbled together what I thought would work but it only works on the essays.lens page and not on the essay.lens or the archive.essay.lens pages, any hints on what I should be doing??

Recent Posts

        {{ essay.published_on date_format="d-m-Y" }}
        {{ essay.title }}  
        


Many thanks</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2015 16:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/10133380</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>newsletter for essays</title>
      <description>Hi,

do you know how I can provide a newsletter to my essays? I think every good blog should have a newsletter ;-)

Thanks for your suggestions.

Kind regards,
Daniel</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2015 11:50:09 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9942528</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>koken:more</title>
      <description>Hi,
I'd like to use the koken:more tag in the essays.lens page to show a selection of recent articles with 'read more' links, however when the user clicks into archive.essays.lens I'd like to disable the koken:more tag to show the full articles. My problem is that if I just delete the token:more bit, it simply deletes the 'read more' link but doesn't show the full article. 
I've been going around in circles, is it possible??
Thanks
Lucie</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2015 09:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9926587</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Slideshow-Pause, deleting and changing of meta data </title>
      <description>Hi, 

I have this slideshow under "Essays". It is an editorial article. But when it runs and runs and runs, you cannot read it. It is not a picture slideshow. Can I get a pause anywhere for mine?

Then I want to change the names of the pictues, like "NeptunLowRes.JPG". Ist this possible or do I have to upload again if I want new ones?

Last question. When I go on a picture in my current theme "Regale", it shows the camera details. I do not want that. Any ideas?

Here's my website, you can have a look what I mean: www.danadolata.de</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2015 08:34:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9915466</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>changing the layout of an essay / page</title>
      <description>Hi guys

I've got several pages set up with images, text, code and Slideshows.
Each is entered in to a  box / section. 
All too often I would like to add another box / section above one I've already entered, but there does not seem any way to add one above a current line or reorder the boxes / sections
This means I have to copy / paste what I can or start again with selection of images / slideshows etc.

Is there an easier way to add  / arrange / re arrange the sections that make up a page / essay?
Is this something that you can fix in  a new iteration of Koken because it does make it harder to re arrange sections once you've committed content to the page.

thanks guys.</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2015 08:15:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9909276</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Save Page as draft</title>
      <description>Hi,
if I change the status of a page from published to draft, the page disappears from koken backend.

Can anyone confirm this with version: 0.19.3   


Cheers
Ralf</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Feb 2015 07:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9859629</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>lightbox navigation button</title>
      <description>Hi,

I am using Boulevard theme for my website. The lightbox has left and right arrow buttons to navigate to the other photos. How can I disable / hide this buttons?</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2014 14:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9843810</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sort in Featured Essays (since 0.19.2 update)</title>
      <description>The sort icon (next to the featured star and delete icon) within the Featured Essays section seems to have been removed.

The sort dialogue box at the bottom of the page says 'manual' but is greyed out and not a clickable element.

Is there a new way to sort the order of Featured Essays that I'm missing?</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 19:26:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9815452</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Use images in essay that align to grid instead of full width</title>
      <description>Hi,

I would like to arrange two or three images next to each other in essays instead of all images being full width. Is there an easy way to do this already?

I am about to create my own theme, so the bare minimum would be to be able to assign custom css classes to individual images so that I can use a css grid based e.g. on a 12 column grid and have normal text and images fill all 12 columns but being able to do diptychs by using 6 and 6 column images or triptychs of 4:4:4 columns or combinations of landscape and portrait images with .e.g 4:8 column spans.

Has anyone done something like this in a koken theme alread? Or course, the deluxe version would be a special interface that allows one to insert an "image row" and allows the user to drag and drop images into diptychs, triptychs etc.

I have found this plugin ( https://www.brisoft.de/en/insert-images-essays-posts/ ) which does something related, but is not really an ideal solution.

Any hints on how to do this would be appreciated. If there is currently no easy way to do this and there are others out there who would like this then let me know and I will consider writing a tutorial on how to do this if I manage or create a plugin for the more comfortable case.

BTW: Thanks for making koken, it looks great so far!

Daniel</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2014 15:01:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9814439</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bug in Page publishing after setting its status to Draft</title>
      <description>Hi,

First of all thanks for the wonderful job you do with Koken.
I find out a bug in Pages publishing section, after having published a page and modified it (HTML) I set it to draft status, but the orange button on the lower right corner that appears normally is not... I found this button recreating a new blank page and passing its status to Draft as well. I could copy/paste my article in a new page, but I'll loose the link (that is already in my comms). So my copyright page is in 404 now...
What can I do to help ? do you need any infos ?</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2014 22:42:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9743291</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pages Regale 2</title>
      <description>Hi there!
when there are multiple images on a page, there is always a distance of about 50 pixels in between. Is it possible to set the distance to zero? to make it more clear, here a screenshot: http://i57.tinypic.com/jsioug.jpg

thx</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 07:17:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9686425</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Isolated pages</title>
      <description>Hello there,

Finally getting my first Koken site up and running using Digital Ocean as a host. I was just curious if I could make a certain page work. 

I'm trying to have one special page, that I could email a link to others and when they enter it into their browser they get this page but NO navigation to other pages on the site. I can't seem to create a page that lacks the header navigation, and so it's easy to get around the site no matter what. Yes, I'm actually trying to make navigation more difficult! (but only for one page)

Thanks for your help,
PS Yes this is the first site I've ever built myself! Figuring out DNS was... interesting </description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2014 22:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9663095</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>blog preview</title>
      <description>Is there a way for my blog page to show just short preview and a "read more" on the Axis 1 theme? I'd rather readers not have to scroll through the entire blog. Thanks!
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2014 15:27:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9638111</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Text Editor tweaks.</title>
      <description>While working with essay/page editor I found out a couple missing features.

! Hard Spaces / Non-breaking spaces in WYSIWYG editor:

Currently the only way to add/view hard spaces in the editor is to edit the code. Most editors have the ability to add hard spaces to the text by pressing Ctrl+Shift+Space. This feature is quite important at least for me, because I justify text in my custom theme I made for a client (http://designdolnoslaski.pl/pages/projekt/). It would be also nice if there was some indication of custom HTML character being present.

! Ctr+Alt+L and Polish Ł character:

Currently Ctrl+Alt+L is used by the editor. Meanwhile Alt-Gr (Ctrl+Alt) is being used for inputing special Polish characters. Alt-Gr+L (Ctrl+Alt+L) is used for inputing Ł character, therefore the binding must be changed, or there must be an option to change it.

! Weird paragraphs:

It's probably not a direct WYSIWYG editor problem, but the inport problem. Currently for some reason, the editor seems to be adding unnecessary paragraphs (''). Here's an essay code sample:  http://pastebin.com/R69fpgxd and the page output http://pastebin.com/CfxxRmgs as can be seen on http://designdolnoslaski.pl/pages/projekt/

! Leftovers -  It seems that the editor leaves behind some  tags setting font-size to 1em (which is pointless)

Custom tags and styles:

It would be nice if I could specify certain tags, and how should they behave in the editor (through for example a stylesheet asset) for clients use. So I wouldn't need to use the code so much.

Alternatively ability to set up a third party text editor for koken use.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 03:00:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9550852</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>background item</title>
      <description>Hi,
i tried to put a image in the background of my webside with css

body {
background:#fff url(../graphics/body_pic.jpg) 0 0 no-repeat;
}

The picture got this size 1920px x 523px
but on the webside it´s only publiced with the size 1920px x 290px.
Can i expand the size of the background picture or is there a possibility to
put an image in the background of the header or the footer?

header {
background:#fff url(../graphics/head_pic.jpg) 0 0 no-repeat;
}
didn´work.
Thanks
Timo

</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 02:55:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9546739</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Customize Image Layout in Essays</title>
      <description>Dear Todd, Brad, and Lauren,

If not already requested, I'd like to submit the following request for a simple image layout customization in essays. Right now, the image(s) added are shown vertical top to down.

My suggestion is modeled after Tumblr. If you upload two images, you could either make it default (top-to-down) or displayed adjacently (diptych). If you upload three, you can drag around for the following combination:

1st Row: Large Image
2nd Row: Diptych

1st Row: Triptych

Etc.

How do you feel about this? Do you think it's practical for your users? More importantly, how is the coding? Is it complex? Relatively doable.?

Thank you,

Ronald</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2014 02:45:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9543169</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to hide "Permalink" in essay &amp; neighbour links to next essay in CSS?</title>
      <description>Hi,
Koken is really great! Congrats.
But I´ve got a main navigation in Repertoire and I´d like to feature my stories in the essays
on the left as you can see: http://www.koken.simone-m-neumann.de/

How to hide the word "Permalink" in CSS (or even rename it)? And
what I have to do in CSS to hide the neighbour links in the essay in CSS?

Could somebody help, please? I nerarly finished my site...!
Thanks a lot and bests regards from Germany!
Simone</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 21:18:25 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9532309</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom Sites</title>
      <description>Hi,

Did Koken provide the option to create custom sites like a contact form or maybe a small shopping cart?
I have built a own site for Contacting me and it worked very well - exept updating the theme I've used.
After deleteing this page, I also could install the theme updates...

So It would be nice if koken gets a way to do such things within the admin-panel

Regards,
Chris</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 22:31:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9518708</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Embedding a Google Calendar</title>
      <description>Hello,

I have a problem with embedding my Google Calendar into my website. When I make a new page in the "text"-module and paste the code, Google gave me for embedding, everything is fine, the calendar is shown. But when I open the published page it is all blank. Is there anyone, who had the same problem and knows, how to solve it?

Thanks for your help,

Paul from Germany</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 16:15:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9492379</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Scheduling Blog Posts</title>
      <description>Is there a way to schedule blog posts for future dates? </description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2015 12:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9467450</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>No essay entry in admin panel ...</title>
      <description>hello,

this is an essay and published: http://www.knut-anstoetz.de/essays/2014/10/shooting-vor-dem-stuttgarter-schloss/

but i want change something and do not find then in the list.

koken say 5 essags, but 4 essays are in the list.

can you help me?

thx
knut</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 17:46:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9424762</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>essay.url blank - urgent!</title>
      <description>Hi there, I'm working on a custom theme to basically show an index of essays (title text), each wrapped in a link to each essay.  This is easily shown in the tutorial pages, yet my URLs for essays are blank.  They're published live, they have titles, IDs, I can't see any issue.  I tried outputting {{ essay.url }} and nothing shows for any of them.

I just clean re-installed Koken.  I'm on Yosemite on a retina macbook pro.

Thanks, I'm hoping to launch on Monday!  I thought this basic step would be a no-brainer.

Best,
Arlo</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 16:53:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9275775</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Media Bar not showing up after pasting text in text editor</title>
      <description>Hi, 

I love Koken, it makes my life easier. However, one small thing bugs me when writing essays.

I pre-write my essays quite often on the go in Notepad, Microsoft Word or on the iPad as an Email. Later, when I try to copy &amp; paste the written text into Koken's text editor, I find that the media bar doesn't show up anymore. It only does show up, when write the entire essay from start in Koken's text editor. (Doesn't matter which browser by the way, I tried IE, Firefox and Chrome. Firefox is my usual standard browser).

This phenomenon has been described earlier (but wasn't solved for me) here:
http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/876867-inserting-image-media-after-pasting-text-into-page

Maybe there is a way to add a "import from word" or notepad or whatever functionality? Or maybe there is a workaround?

Thanks for the help!
Cheers,
Andy

I use the Axis theme (though it doesn't seem like a theme thing) and the newest version of Koken. 
My website's adress is: www.andygrabo.de</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 22:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9174104</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Categories Tab in Navigation</title>
      <description>Hi There,

I'm hoping to add a "categories" menu item to my navigation that organizes essays/blog entries. Ideally, the "categories" menu item would be a dropdown allowing me to click a category type and land on a page with an index of that category's essays. I'm assigning categories to essays and using the Observatory template. 

Thanks! 

Elise </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 15:33:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/9104152</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Timeline Render Issues for Essay Page</title>
      <description>Hi - I'm using "Repertoire" theme on my site. I made an "essay" with few images in it. When I go to essay section I can see it properly. That works as expected.

However when I go to timeline, it shows this essay entry in following format:




and then

{{ content.title }}{{ content.caption }}

template placeholder for whatever number of images I attached to that essay.

Do you know why this is happening? should I turn on/off some option to make it go away?

See it here: http://mementories.com/timeline/

Thanks.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2014 01:26:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/8631282</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Essay page order</title>
      <description>Hi Todd, 
I have re-ordered our essay pages, but my recent post ( Handbag Cannon ) stays in the last position, rather the the first.

Not sure if there is a place to hit "Publish" first to make the new order stick ?

Regards,
David</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 11:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/8620523</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>pages not loading in admin section</title>
      <description>Hello, I am desperately trying to understand why my pages created in Text section don't load in my admin space. I cannot edit them nor delete them. Although they appear in "Site" and I can even  add them to my navigation. there's no way for me to retrieve these pages to edit. Essays are fine. Pages are blocked somewhere, I can create more and more pages but don't know where they all go, the "inspector" keep showing the "You do not have any saved drafts", below the window shows "5 items"... and the little wheel keep spinning, on and on...
Going nuts over here!
Thanks for your help</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2014 02:02:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/8599172</link>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
