<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>help.koken.me :: Themes</title>
    <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/topics/696978-themes</link>
    <description>Themes articles</description>
    <item>
      <title>Movers and Packers in delhi  blog pasting Shifting</title>
      <description>viste here :- Movers and Packers in delhi @http://professionalmovers.in/packers-and-movers-in-delhi/

Execu-move is a experienced Packers and Movers in delhi company worth trusting. The company require removals of furniture and different articles from the offices or homes. Little properties with single room or enormous business place, that company removes all of the articles properly and knowledge so that all and every material is sent noise without finding missing or damaged. Execu-move not merely does the work of removal nationally but additionally internationally. That is one enormous possibility of having related with this particular company.

1 Residential Activities


That skilled Packers and Movers in delhi company does the work of residential move with significantly swiftness and successfully which usually is fairly a time intensive and difficult work. The company does that work for their consumers to have the ability to reduce their problem and let them have promise in regards to the secure and hassle free way to obtain house what to the destined place. The packers and movers package your loved ones points with high quality providing products and services so that your points are sent properly with no injury or misplacement.

2 International Activities


Probably the most tight accomplish is separation many other the main state or many other state altogether. Execu-move offers the consumers with the ability of world wide removals. With assistance from successful Packers and Movers delhi, high quality providing program and strategies the business enterprise may promise secure and noise removal and carriage of items from any house or business to any the main world. The world wide removal program is fairly successful as a result of progress of various new strategies regarding removal system.

Delivery: The experienced Packers and Movers in delhi company helps the people to find the method of transport in the event of world wide experienced Packers and Movers in delhi. It offers their consumers the benefit of home to home company, that is main worldwide. That company requires provisions like, reprofessional Packers and Movers in delhi of packages, unpacking all of the articles, placing and placing the furniture properly, beach freight, and significantly more. Really the cars of the consumers are often moved properly to the destined place anywhere in that world.

Delivery pots: Different styles of pots is found wherever your loved ones points and transports must certanly be carried.

3 Organization Activities

Execu-move makes for removal of business articles in a successful and skilled manner. That experienced Packers and Movers in delhi company is capable of reprofessional Packers and Movers in delhi articles from various kinds of offices be it little or enormous offices having adjustable floors. The of use documents and papers from perform are first packed and sent safely. Your different business articles are removed and sent in the most secured way possible. Such business activities will require place internationally as well when perform all together is moved to another the main earth or any other the main country.

Be it residential activities or business activities, Execu-move, the skilled Movers and Packers in delhi company, is the better in the business.
When you employ the company with this company, you are able to stay confident that the content may truly be sent by yourself preferred place with no delay or damage. If you wish to have significantly more reliable shows, then you can truly only see the online evaluations supplied by several people of the company.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 11:24:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14315556</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Great Post Packers and Movers in noida article</title>
      <description>viste here:-Movers and packers Noida @ http://professionalmovers.in/packers-and-movers-in-nodia/

It's an built-in specific inclination and maintain competent Packers and Movers in Noida business in one place to the other. Even yet in initially time, at that time when man was previously a hunter-gatherer, he used competent Packers and Movers in Noida business in one destination for a still another in search of larger surroundings. But, it's not very easy to change in to a brand new place. All of the conditions it's mainly because we do not need enough information about one of the most up-to-date engineering which may aid in competent Packers and Movers in Noida business as an example competent Packers and Movers in Noida business pods, competent Packers and Movers in Noida business pots, storage pods etc. These records which until recently was available simply to the great corporate agencies is currently available to others too. It's produced the complete procedure for competent Packers and Movers in Noida business your stuff in one position to another a straightforward job.


The most used method that will be placed on qualified Movers and packers in Noida business household items around good ranges is competent Packers and Movers in Noida business containers. As set alongside the unsteady card dining table bins by which people only push in the products, competent Packers and Movers in Noida business pots actually really are a larger option. Because they are produced from material, competent Packers and Movers in Noida business pots assure security to your goods. The chance of harm is compensated down and also the damage of the goods could be reduced. many times, it's problematic for you to definitely operate with competent Packers and Movers in Noida business pots on the own. To simply help them this way, solutions by packers and movers may be employed.

 

Likewise, anyone has the chance of using competent Packers and Movers in Noida business pods rather than containers. They're smaller tested, more compact and more user-friendly. In competent Packers and Movers in Noida business pods, pods are still another term for Lightweight On Need Storage. Usually, the meaning of competent Packers and Movers in Noida business pots is applied interchangeably with that of competent Packers and Movers in Noida business pods but equally obviously have a couple of distinctions. The products are usually slipped at your house when you telephone for competent Packers and Movers in Noida business pods. You'll then be asked to fill them along along with your home goods.

 

On still another give, given that the pods are little, you may choose one up and do the transport also on your own, ergo in influence placing an end to the prerequisite of a movers and packers company. But, there may be conditions wherever you just need to store what exactly and definitely not maintain them in one destination for a another. Such instances, the goods to be correctly used are storage pods, which obviously are often applied interchangeably with competent Packers and Movers in Noida business pods and competent Packers and Movers in Noida business containers. Storage pods enable you to put on large amounts of home goods in a tiny space, such storage pods might then be used in a non-descript position as you inhabit your self with decorating the home or giving in anything such as for instance a major situation or food table.

 

It's probable to only fill these pods on the rear of the vehicle and switching it around great ranges but you have the decision of competent Packers and Movers in Noida business pods especially for that goal. Merely talking, every one of the three products - competent Packers and Movers in Noida business pots, qualified Packers and Movers in Noida business pods and storage pods - have related functions. These items have several distinctions and therefore are very similar to each other. In case that you discover ways to utilize them efficiently, qualified Packers and Movers Noida business and giving could possibly be an incredibly simple work for you.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 11:22:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14315555</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>One of the most useful writers Packers and Movers in Bangalore posts</title>
      <description>viste here:-http://professionalmovers.in/packers-and-movers-in-bangalore/

top twenty skilled movers and packers bangalore business Moving might be a great knowledge if the procedure is straightforward and comfortable. There are lots of top twenty skilled Packers and Movers in Bangalore business businesses available. The task before someone trying to find businesses is not to find one but to choose one. Obviously, the companies are normal we will not discover somewhat big difference within their packages. To offer an agreement to anything oriented business is what any customer wants. When any provider shows professionalism and a commitment in a work together than he's called to become excellent organisation and because of the quality and devotion in perform can be the first choice.


The specific qualities what type should search for in any Packers and Movers Bangalore businesses are the following:


The consistency may be the foremost important quality needed in a vendor. This really is towards both when career and client. They should be committed towards their perform and authentic towards the commitment. Manager should manage to offer a whole defense to someone or perhaps a client. The safety procedures like insurance may also be crucial these days. The insurance from the provider gives a large level of satisfaction and comfort to a customer. A hassle free, tension free moving is a desire any specific who is choosing relocation. The punctuality of both team and government using their support is what one is definitely seeking for. Any company gratifying these criteria's should be a choice for just about any vendor but envision if we could have significantly more?


There are lots of top twenty skilled Movers and packers in Bangalore business businesses which provide significantly more than this. They realize the significance of your belongings to be shifted. An excellent and trusted organisation never believes in giving surprises. The correct view is provided by them before any check out a fresh destination. A fruitful top twenty skilled movers and packers bangalore business completely is influenced by packing. Reveal supplying recommendations and support is presented thus that the merchandise are secure and safe. The supervisor who is provided the job should be involved from the shift before the ultimate destination. If any organisation makes this techniques than it's for certain the client who when needed businesses from their keep will not go to any for the supplying and top twenty skilled Movers and packers Bangalore business services. Generally, vacations are chosen for a shift and organisations test to obtain useful advantage of the selection by obtaining additional but a person oriented business will not rely on these little earnings. The client convenience can be their matter and priority. Nowadays, we've the most powerful 10 skilled movers and packers bangalore business support providers who offer a whole comfort and satisfaction to the client and also help whole performance by getting all the newest techniques within their working.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 11:21:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14315553</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Safe and Affordable Removals Gurgaon</title>
      <description>visit here article post:- Packers and Movers in Gurgaon@ http://professionalmovers.in/packers-and-movers-in-gurgaon/

Packers and Movers Gurgaon things is surely an high priced work, if you're using professional Packers and Movers Gurgaon organizations to go things that you might change yourself. Ahead of contacting a packer and mover, you'll need to produce a list of things you will need to get and then assault those items for that you merely need professional Packers and Movers Gurgaon service.


Packers and Movers Gurgaon things from position to some other becomes a easy, when you yourself have a Packers and Movers in Gurgaon to appear after your goods. Packers and Movers Gurgaon things is really a class power and the group includes qualified group, filling and Packers and Movers Gurgaon extras and vehicles. Packers and Movers Gurgaon begins with filling of things and before filling, you've to produce a list of things looking packing.


You are able to class many things in a field and in this manner save your self your own time and labor. Loading a lot of things at one position preserves time and labor as you are able to change the products at one go. If you need to be filling each item individually you then must change each class individually. It is merely a filling and Packers and Movers Gurgaon group that can group things for packing. Products which are similar in efficiency and ease might be loaded together but there are numerous facets that you'll need to take into account when clubbing things for packing.


Movers and packers in Gurgaon things is surely an high priced work, if you're using professional Packers and Movers Gurgaon organizations to go things that you might change yourself. Ahead of contacting a packer and mover, you'll need to produce a list of things you will need to get and then assault those items for that you merely need professional Packers and Movers Gurgaon service. Making a list of things you need to change with assistance from professional help may also help in obtaining cost estimates from filling and Packers and Movers Gurgaon companies.


When you know, which things you need to change and just how many things exist to get; you are able to negotiate a cope with a Packers and Movers in Gurgaon. For example you are able to use help on variable charges to truly save lots of money, while Packers and Movers Gurgaon your things in a safe manner. Or you can get professional Packers and Movers Gurgaon help on a fix cost and have peace of mind.
Advantageous asset of Packers and Movers Gurgaon things with a Packers and Movers in Gurgaon is you get surety of protection of one's goods. Qualified organizations are protected therefore the service provider may pay the injury in case there is accidents and normal calamities. In that fashion, you should have reassurance following handing about your of good use what to a specialist elimination company.


You are able to contact a Movers and packers Gurgaon to provide you with a cost estimate for his services. The professional can visit your home, establish the quantity of conduct, calculate the cost and provide you with a cost quote. In that fashion, you are able to obvious any miscommunication which may arise by finding a cost estimate on the cornerstone of list.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 11:17:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14315551</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Spacing Galerie Grid</title>
      <description>Hey guys, 

I`m using the Axis 2 Theme and was wondering:
My first gallery page has two sets. Now, is it possible to space only two sets so that they are centered. I can't seem to find a way to do that. At the moment it`s  right centered...which just looks totally off. 

Thanks!

Melanie

</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 15:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14312417</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Responsive design in combination with forwarded domain</title>
      <description>Dear all

I have installed koken on my website www.lehner.info/ml. When I open this site it opens the 
- desktop design when I open it from my notebook and it opens the 
- mobile design when I open it from my smartphone. 
So everything works as intended.

But I have also configured a domain forward from my domain www.martinlehner.com which redirects to www.lehner.info/ml where the domain name www.martinlehner.com remains. In this case the desktop design appears even if I open it from my smartphone.

Does anybody know why koken doesn’t recognise the smartphone correctly in this case?
Any idea how to fix this issue?

Thanks a lot, Martin  
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 20:38:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14310161</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get rid of the "download" link in Axis?</title>
      <description>Hey there,

just changed my theme from Regale to Axis and was wondering if there was a way to get rid of the Download Button underneath the images?
Like here for example: http://koken.sophiesaller.de/preview.php?/albums/tini-uli-1/content/cu-best-123/

Thanks in advance and kind regards,

Sophie</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2015 21:37:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14307315</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Celine Bag to find a luxurious</title>
      <description>Trip Preparation Tips In our Choosing and Booking section, you can locate information about finding lodging and flights. For example, you can [b][url=http://www.celinehandbagsonline.com/celine-trapeze-c-25/]Celine Trapeze Bag[/url][/b] read about how to find cheap hostels or how to find a luxurious villa overseas, how to book tickets for entertainment, and, of course, how to locate and book flights online.

Our Gearing Up and Health Safety sections provide you with tons of advice on what to take with you depending on the destination, how to avoid a shark [b][url=http://www.celinehandbagsonline.com/celine-mini-tie-c-29/]Celine Mini Tie Handbag[/url][/b] attack, and any other travelrelated topic in between.

Everything you need to know about [b][url=http://www.celinehandbagsonline.com/celine-phantom-c-24/]Celine Phantom Cabas[/url][/b] maps and destinations you can find in our Guides and Maps section. Besides obvious advice on how to read a map, there are also articles about using an ATM abroad and about entertainment in different parts of the world.

The Packing section shows you how to pack enough for your vacation and still be within airlines' security and weight guidelines. This section also advises you on the luggage restrictions and how to find this information. Our Paperwork section deals with everything related to documents that you need for your travel, from passports to visas.

The site's Planning and Trips sections show how to successfully plan your vacation, whether it's a day trip or a month in New Zealand. These sections give you advice on everything from fixing a broken case handle to using international calling cards. If you're planning a trip of any kind, our website is the perfect onestop shop for any travel information you [b][url=http://www.celinehandbagsonline.com/]Celine Bag[/url][/b] may need!

http://www.valentinoshoesa.com/valentino-sandals-c-13/
http://www.valentinorockstudsale.com/valentino-tote-bags-c-9/
http://www.lhbon.com/celine-micro-luggage-c-13_19/
http://www.airjordanmvp.com/nike-kobe-8-c-102/
http://www.lhbon.com/burberry-hobo-c-193_196/</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 14:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14302445</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightbox - Cross-fading without black phase</title>
      <description>In the lightbox the cross-fading from image to image looks bad. Switching to the next image fades the current image to black and then the new image fades in. It is possible to eliminate the black phase?  It would be nice, if the current image could fade directly into the next image without black phase. 

This unpleasant image cross-fading I can see in the lightbox of all demo themes. Is there any solution?</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Sep 2015 10:31:52 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14301933</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulevard-Theme Aspect-Ration wrong</title>
      <description>Hey there,

somebody noticed, that the image-aspect (ratio) in the feature-slide is not the same as in the album-slides in boulevard theme? why? am i missing something? i mean people look em.. wide.. inspected the lens stuff etc and saw, that the difference between featured and album slides is.. yes aspect..! 

So anybody knows how to fix this?

cheers
Chris</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2015 14:22:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14296232</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Disable Splash Screen for Mobile</title>
      <description>Hello!

Regarding Madison 2 Theme, I was wondering if there was a way to disable the splash screen front page for mobile, so that it only shows up on desktop.

It doesn't work too well on phones (the pictures slide, as opposed to dissolve), plus the logo disappears.  Mobile looks far better as single-column Grid (if you want that full-screen look).

Thanks!</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 21:50:27 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14272488</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Italics</title>
      <description>Hello,

On my site, I present among others photos of animals and plants using the Latin scientific name of species. The rule is that this name should be in italics.

If I put the names between tags (....) in the title and caption fields of the Library, the names are italicized in the title, but not in the caption. Furthermore the tags appear as such in the browser tabs.

Is there a way to change this?</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 15:55:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14271218</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Change navigation buttons on lightbox in Madison2</title>
      <description>Hello,

I changed the background colour of the lightbox to white (via CMS). Is it possible to change also the colour of the navigation buttons. The problem is that they are almost invisible (very light grey) on the white background.

Thank you in advance for your answer. </description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2015 07:05:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14271184</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Own js and css in Template</title>
      <description>Hi, i like to use mmenu for Template Elemantary.

I put js file in folder js and css file in folder css.

In header.html i insert:

        
        
        

But it doesn`t load. I like to have this css and js on all sites in this template.

THX</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 10:23:30 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14265402</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Copy to Home and Album pages</title>
      <description>Hi,

How do I add some introduction copy to the top of the home page and Album page?

I'm using the Elementary theme.

Thanks
Jason</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 18:35:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14259826</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regale 2 photo display question</title>
      <description>Hello,

I recently purchased Regale 2.
I would like to show the photo's in my blog in a similar way as you show in the example site on: http://madison.koken.me/essays/

I would like to show my blog photo's in Regale 2 exactly the same as the example. I mean with the boxes arounf the photo and title.
Can you tell me if this is possible and how?

cheers
Danny Zuurbier</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 18:14:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14255186</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulevard - Mobile browser - horizontal bug?</title>
      <description>Hey Koken team!
First off thank you for continuing to build and 
support such an amazing platform.

http://okiave.com/albums/c0ec19e8b744ffe8ae9852879ab362a9/

I'm using Boulevard and noticed that on my iPhone6 chrome
browser that the gallery will treat the last image of the album
as a new block element  instead of running it inline with the others.

When I flip the phone to vertical view this issue doesn't exist.
Hope this feedback is of use. Thanks</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Aug 2015 07:42:56 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14249054</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>boulevard theme favorites - option to enlarge photo by clicking on it?</title>
      <description>Hello, 

I am using the boulevard theme and displaying my "favorites" for the main page. The default setting seems to be that when you click an image it makes the page scroll to the right. 

I am wondering if there is an option to change this, so if you click on an image it simply enlarges the it? 
I would be happy with only the scroll bar and the navigation buttons as options to scroll left and right if this meant i could have this option. Or, is there some other way it can be an option to see photos bigger using the favorites?

Thanks!!

Lilly</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 18:15:19 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/14248695</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Axis2 Theme - Picture display</title>
      <description>Hello,

I apologize, if this turns out to be a typical beginner's question.

I bought Axis2, created sets (the typical thing - landscape, people, vacations...) and a number of albums under each set.
I can manage to display all albums of a set on one screen (finally I found the grid parameter), but when I click on a certain album, all pictures from that album appear one below the other (list view ?), not as I wish 6, 9 or 12 on a page. Even after hours and a lot of coffee, I can't find the magic switch to turn this on.

The functionality is shown on the Axis2 reference at http://timwrate.com.au/albums/, so I'm sure, there must be a way...

Any advice would be very much appreciated!

Best regards,
Mario</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 12:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13774690</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>lightbox too transparent</title>
      <description>Hello,

Is there a way to make the lightbox background less transparent? According to the environmental/computer light, one can see partly the page underneath the lightbox background. This is a kind of disturbance when looking at the pictures in the lightbox.

N.B. I am using Madison 2 on a MacBook Pro with Retina.

Thanks in advance for your answer.

</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 18:49:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13698103</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Installing a Theme</title>
      <description>I want to install your Elementary theme.  I click on Install and I go to the login page.  I am logged in already. How do I install the Elementary theme?  My installation is: http://jkpx.com/koken/.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 15:05:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13272228</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>themes</title>
      <description>in put photos themes</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2015 17:54:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13224742</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>lazy loading pulse theme repertoire</title>
      <description>Hi,

I use repertoire theme feature for my albums page http://cpixel.fr/sets/bw-1/
When a page is open, I cas see in network dev tools that all content is loaded.
How to add lazy loading for pulse ?

Thx</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 15:06:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13080475</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulevard Favorite Page?</title>
      <description>Hello! Reading through this page solved 90% of my issue: http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/8412365-boulevard-featured-content 

.... But is there any change to the favorites page where a click on the image would take the user to the Album where it's placed?

Thanks!</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 23:51:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13071098</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madison 2</title>
      <description>When i try to install Madison 2,  apears permanently this message:

&lt;&gt;  </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 09:50:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13063949</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulevard, viewport doesn't work in galleries?!</title>
      <description>I just noticed that the viewport on gallery-sites doesn't really work as intended, the site seems like it's too far zoomed out, pictures are small and even the title is smaller than text pages or album pages. 

Is there any way I can make sure the gallery sites are on the same zoom level like the rest text-pages?

Open these sites on a mobile device and you'll see what I mean:
Gallery:
http://ivansuta.ch
Text:
http://ivansuta.ch/pages/ueber/</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 10:35:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13055786</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Koken:If only through Javascript</title>
      <description>Hello, am I wrong, or it appears that koken:if works by hiding pieces of html through Javascript? Is there any way to do that on server side?

Thanks,
J</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2015 07:09:24 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13050223</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Can't install theme</title>
      <description>On a test server I used to buy and activate the theme Axis 2
When the site began at the main site and install the theme, then the system displays a message https://yadi.sk/i/Zxw5L5SUiB9iP

When approve the authorization request?</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 11:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/13046878</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Individual templates</title>
      <description>Hello, 

I am using Madison 2.
Is it possible to make "individual templates" per album? For example one showcased in list and one showcased in grid?

It doesn't seem to be supported by theme by default, is it still possible to do it with custom CSS ?

Thank you in advance for your reply

Baz</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2015 21:30:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12998277</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regale 2 - change order of HTML elements</title>
      <description>I'm using a splash screen (full screen gallery) on a scrollable page.

Aside from the fact this may sound nuts, can someone tell me how to put the title and caption as an overlay on the image, rather than as text below?

I have tried the following

.k-content-title {
    margin-top:-270px;
    z-index:999;
}

This works to change position of the title, but the image obscures the text. (I know it's there because between each image fade you see it quickly)

Thanks

Mat</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 13:25:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12985798</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chastain Theme Settings Missing</title>
      <description>I am trying to set up my Chastain Theme to use the triptych layout of my cover photos but the option is missing in my site settings box. ( I can send a snapshot) Under the template tab the only options I get are for elements (lightbox, show title, show caption). I also wanted to set up my albums so they are viewed in a grid pattern but so far all my photos are in one column. www.headshotsbykemp.com

Any help with this would be great!!!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 02:55:11 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12984355</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theme purchase for test domain</title>
      <description>Hi, I'm setting up Koken on a test domain and want to purchase the Regale 2 theme.

I note that when I check out, it recognises the domain, new.matsmithphotography.com

When I'm ready to take the site live, will this theme work on my non-test domain, matsmithphotography.com? Can I purchase the theme now then switch the domain later?

Regards

Mat</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2015 16:29:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12979953</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chastain Theme Image Manipulation</title>
      <description>Hello,

I would like my images to be left as they are, no scaling, no resharpening or anything. Where can I fix that and what exactly do I have to specify?

Regards

Joachim</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 13:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12972497</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OxyGen 1.9.3 available for download!</title>
      <description>My custom theme that I use for my personal Koken site is now ready for download!

This theme has up to now been "exclusive" for visitors to Koken Community Support: but now we want to share the "love" with everybody! ;) :)


Documentation can be found here: http://varoystrand.se/sidor/oxygen/
Downloads can be found at: http://kokensupport.varoystrand.se/viewtopic.php?f=16&amp;t=32
Source code: https://github.com/BlackSkorpio/OxyGen

Hope some of you find it useful, if you do: don't hesitate to tell us by adding your site to our "Showcase your site" listing

----------------------
Regards, Bjarne
Koken Community Support - http://kokensupport.varoystrand.se/</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 16:46:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12949124</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Axis 2</title>
      <description>hello koken team,

is it possible to align the menue and title left and not in the center in the axis 2 theme ?

thanks,

ralf</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 16:45:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12944214</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orginal AXIS Theme</title>
      <description>I do not create a backup before i try to change something now nothing works ... Is there an Way to geht the original Axis theme back ? Where i can download it i cannot find the theme in the store.</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 13:08:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12940337</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>can't access the store</title>
      <description>Hi guys - I can't access the store or store/plugins or store/templates menu on the site.
It defaults back to /library all the time
Any suggestions?</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Aug 2015 05:49:55 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12928276</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regale: Image resizing on album preview?</title>
      <description>Hi there,

is it possible to change the way images are being displayed on album previews? I understand one can change the aspect ratio of that preview image but I have not found a way to resize an image. I mean, if your subject matter is not directly in center, most preview images look horrible. Even if I change the aspect ratio to 1:1 it still won't look alright...

For instance, please check out " http://maxkissler.com/sets/menschen/ " to know what I mean. 

Is there a solution?

Thanks, 
Max Kißler</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 13:07:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12905118</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>two themes in one?</title>
      <description>Hi,

I like the Regale 2 very much, but I'd love to have a horizontal (Boulevard style) gallery as well for my travel photography. The splash full-screen is good, but not what I'm looking for</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2015 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12903337</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Album thumb width in Regale 2</title>
      <description>Hi,

Is it possible to change the Album grid so that the height would always be the same? 
Now it scales the thumbs by the width and the horizontal pictures gets very small.. 
http://nicktulinen.com/albums/mari-perankoski/

otherwise. Very good work! Thank You!</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2015 13:08:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12903325</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Title Display under Image in Axis 2 doesn't fade</title>
      <description>Hi, 
On the Landing Page (Axis 2), the Title Display under my Images doesn't fade, while the images do fade. That creates a strange rupture in the flow of the display. 
Is there anything I can do to make the title appear later or fade as well?  

You can look at it here: www.teresamarenzi.com

Thanks! Teresa
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Aug 2015 09:33:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12900173</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dimension / Ratio in Slideshow (Axis 2)</title>
      <description>Hi,

I am working on my page. My images will be presented with a slide-show. Unfortunately, the ratio / dimension of the slide-show in AXIS 2 can not be changed. There is only a crop (landscape, portrait, ...). If I use "none" the image is shown as a whole, but there is a big margin on top and bottom.

How can I solve this problem?

Alex</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2015 09:39:35 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12879796</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showing multiple albums on the "home" page of Madison 2 theme?</title>
      <description>Hello,

Love Madison 2 theme. Quick question, how do I configure my site:

http://bobandmatt.com/

To show all of the Albums, and not just all of the entries for the first Album as it displays now?

I'm looking to align to this example:

http://robtmann.net/

Since I like how it will display all the Albums when it's responsive to tablet/mobile. With my site right now, all of the Albums get hidden in the flyout nav — so it only looks like I have a few things.

Here is a screengrab of how I have the directory setup. My guess is it's a problem here?

https://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/11368113/Screen%20Shot%202015-06-24%20at%2012.07.20%20PM.png

Thank you!
Bob</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 15:49:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12873944</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madison 2@</title>
      <description>Hi!
I already addressed to you to give me back the money for purchasing the theme "madison2."
Your answer was as follows:
                                                        Bjarne Varöystrand
                                                        May 27, 2015 07:32AM EDT
                                                        You need to send an email to: support@koken.me with your request

                                                         Regards, Bjarne

I wrote to you on e-mail the request, but no one answers me !!!
What is the problem ??
Give me back my money !!!
I refuse to buy madison2</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jun 2015 19:09:26 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12852500</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overly compressed/garbled thumbnails in Regale 2</title>
      <description>Hi!
I'm having issues where some of my thumbnails in Regale 2 are not displaying correctly; out of twenty or so, three or four will be overly compressed and garbled. The full resolution seem to be fine. I'm using ImageMagick 6.7.9-10, but it appears to happen with ImageMagick 6.7.9 and GD Bundled. Could it be something to do with the original JPGs that I'm uploading?

Thanks!</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 14:59:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12848040</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FB icon not aligned in regale theme</title>
      <description>Hi,

My site is www.chetank.com
Iam seeing that the social networks icons are not aligned and also I have enabled share links, but that is also not displayed. Iam an amateur in this field, please help me

Thanks &amp; Regards
Chetan</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 14:59:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12845941</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>space between navigation links</title>
      <description>hey!

how can I add some space between groups of links in the navigation as in the default theme screenshots in the store.

thank you! 

</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 22:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12844247</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cannot Change Theme</title>
      <description>I select a theme. Click use theme. Get a message that the theme has been successfully applied. I am redirected to the Drafts page. There is no visible change to the Drafts page. Cannot click Publish because the button says no changes.</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2015 13:42:36 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12833432</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>madison 2 logo size</title>
      <description>Trying to make my logo larger in your madison 2 theme. Is this possible?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 16:05:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12833118</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fullsize Pictures</title>
      <description>Hi there,

i use the Theme chastain. Is it possible to use a picture as background? And is it possible to open an Album in Fullsize 100% of the Monitor?

Thanx in advance

Marcel </description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 14:51:54 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12823401</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New Themes Not Showing in Themes List</title>
      <description>I tried to install some of the themes from the store (Boulevard and Repertoire). The interface says that the themes have installed correctly, and I can look on my host and see a folder for the theme has been created. However they do not show in the list of themes available for use so I cannot enable them. So far I have tried clearing "koken/storage/cache/api" to no effect.</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jun 2015 17:03:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12814470</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>refund</title>
      <description>Dear people of Koken,

I just bought the "madison 2" product and I made my decision too quickly.
Can I get a refund?

Brice</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 16:39:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12813209</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Examples</title>
      <description>Hi. I published my website. I sent to koken for adding my website as an example. But when i sent offer, my website wasnt ready. So it is ready for example, but i cant offer again. Could you see my website again and ,if you like please add my website as an example. 
Thank you. </description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 14:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12812251</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elementary template shows EXIF model wrong</title>
      <description>In my site there`s few letters of caption in EXIF Model.

Koken 0.21.2

Elementary 1.5.8</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 15:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12808401</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regale 2 Creative Commons Links</title>
      <description>Hi,

is it possible to include the correct Links to the Creative Commons licenses for photos unter that license?
Currently, there is only the name of the license.

Regards
Christian Eiden</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2015 12:33:03 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12800635</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sublink CSS</title>
      <description>http://hofkin.com
Is there CSS that would allow me to modify the sub links?
In the screenshot Medical &amp; General fall under Illustration but need less visual emphasis to show the fall under illustration. Like maybe a flush right indent...?

Screenshot:
https://scontent-sea1-1.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-xft1/v/t34.0-12/11130565_10155599825685319_1984551818_n.jpg?oh=562acb9895d3c3d0bb292e1f593eac39&amp;oe=5574C220</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 01:15:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12784707</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thum dimensions in Regale 2</title>
      <description>Hello, 

Is it possible to change the gallery settings in Regale 2 so that the thumbnails would be always the same height. 
Now i believe it's the other way around and the thumbs are always presented in the same width.

I'd love this modification</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 13:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12783369</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grid template</title>
      <description>Hi there, 
I'm currently using the slideshow to display the photos of each album i have, using the Axis theme.
I tried to add a grid layout to one of the albuns, and it seems like it's not possible to have a separate template for an album/page. It just changes across the entire website.

Is there any option to customise the layout of an album/page? using the grid template instead of the slideshow ?

Thanks, 
Thales</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 07:23:05 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12776342</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Store photos in cloud</title>
      <description>Good day! mosthosting does not give a lot of disk space, tell whether there is a plan to support or store photos in the cloud, for example google drive, dropbox etc?</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 14:59:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12776333</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>align pics</title>
      <description>i use boulevard theme.
But everypics are not on same live 

the last one is under the line..
what can i do ?

you can see on gallery
hashka.fr/photo/albums/flynt/

thanks</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 14:51:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12771656</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theme designs- quirks and bugs</title>
      <description>I have high hopes (and wishes) for what you folks are doing. Thanks!   I've been using a few of the free themes on my site http://jrileystewart.com for several weeks. Always looking for that perfect theme, and am willing to pay for it, but seemingly simple quirks in the themes I've tried so far is keeping me from committing to a purchase. Just not confident that I'll not be stuck with the same limitations I see with your free themes. 

-Found Elementary theme to meet most of my needs. Also have published using Axis.  I like that I can turn off all the BS I don't want to show (like EXIF, date captured, etc -- no one cares about that stuff and professional looking sites don't include such). I really like the layout of Repertoire and Madison, but I can't turn off the BS with those templates. Wish I could.  
- Also, when I tried to use an image as header for the Repertoire template, it placed the image BELOW the links. What's with that?  (I'm using Chrome, maybe it's an issue only with that browser, don't know). 

If you can, it might be a valuable improvement to enable turning on/off ALL of the text fields for EACH template. Currently enabling/disabling seems to be all over the place, depending on which theme you use. If you could confirm that the paid templates give me that flexibility, I'd be willing to buy some of them. 
Thanks for listening. 
Jim
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2015 14:51:04 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12771409</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madison 2 - Center site title to content</title>
      <description>Hi all,

I have little/no knowledge of CSS and PHP so I've been figuring it out as I go along.

I've moved the site title on Madison 2 from the navigation bar, to above the content area. My current struggle however, is getting it to stay centered even when the images/browser window are scaled down.

So far I am only able to accomplish either of the following:

1) Centered above the content window, but will stay in the same place and will not reorient when browser is resized.

2) Centered over the entire browser window no matter how it is scaled, but will not centered over the content. (I hope that makes sense)

I would appreciate any help in the matter; below is the CSS for where I am now and screenshots for the former.

#floatinglogo {
	margin-left:calc([$col_width]px + [$main_side_pad_in]px);
	width:[$contents_max_col_width]px;
	
	text-align: center;
	overflow: visible;
	position: fixed;
	z-index: 10;	
}

http://imgur.com/a/gTNNH (1st - full content size, 2nd - scaled down)

I really appreciate all of you taking the time to read through this at the very least!</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2015 20:45:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12753639</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madison 2 - Show Title/Caption on thumbs on mouseover</title>
      <description>Hey there,

I'm using Koken and the Madison 2 Theme - it's great!!
One question:

is it possible to show Titel and Caption on the Thumbnails on mouseover?

It is possible in Regale, and it would be great if it would be available for Madison, too.
Thanks,

Dominik</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 21:41:13 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12753394</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Download image in Regale 2</title>
      <description>Hi,

I am pretty sure that there was an option to enable downloads within the lightbox. But I am not sure if this is also feasible with Regale 2 theme. At least, I cannot find it.

Could you help me on this?

Thx lot, Thilo</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 15:11:49 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12739693</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>madison 2 !!!</title>
      <description>Bjarne Varöystrand
May 22, 2015 07:19AM EDT
Hi Max.
Please keep questions in english...

Yoo can only use the theme on one domain: if you want to use it on another site, you need to deactivate it on site #1 to be able to use it on site #2.

Hi!
Please give me back the money for the theme "madison2." !!!
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 15:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12737306</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chastain image link/ligthbox link</title>
      <description>When I click on image in album with "Link images to lightbox" setting enabled I get empty lightbox. If I disable this setting I get just empty page. Can you help me, please?</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2015 19:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12735838</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulevard problem with horizontal slide (using Chrome)</title>
      <description>Hi there,

I've been using Koken for a few months, quite happy with it.
I installed the Boulevard theme because of the cool horizontal slider.

But...and I don't know when this started -because I noticed this just a few days ago-, the horizontal slider isn't working properly in Chrome anymore.
The last photo drops vertical instead of staying with the rest on one horizontal line.
It looks fine using Firefox and IE, but it's still very annoying since this wasn't going on earlier.
I installed the theme again, but that wasn't the solution.

It seems this problem existed in the past but has been fixed.
Now it seems has returned, maybe after the updates on the themes?

Thanks for your response!



</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 14:25:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12734417</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Form</title>
      <description>Several of my clients have been asking for a contact form to ask basic questions instead of booking a free consultation appointment. Is there anyway Koken can either have a plug in or directions/instructions or even ccs codes for koken users to add a contact form? I am on the edge of switching to another provider due to this issue! I paid to have my page customize and still not able to get the contact form. Also I just purchased a theme that I would like a refund on. The Receipt ID is489CBFM. Thanks!</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 May 2015 18:03:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12729968</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boulevard theme error?</title>
      <description>Hi Koken, 

I use Boulevard theme for my site: lianggono.com

I chose Boulevard because its capability to show an endless slide of images beautifully.
But recently, I came across my 'Works' page the last image on slideshow stacked up 
at the bottom of the screen, and it's ugly. (see preview) http://lianggono.com/works/elle-decoration-2/

This behavior could kills Boulevard's main strength,
could you guys help me on this?</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2015 16:15:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12716010</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>madison 2</title>
      <description>Добрый день! Я купил у вас тему "madison 2"  можно ли ее использовать для двух разных сайтов?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 11:31:46 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12714106</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chastain on mobile</title>
      <description>Hi - I'm having the same issue addressed here: 
http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/1032827-chastain-on-mobile

Was a solution found? The logo/image is off center to the right when viewed portrait on mobile. It appears to be due to the width of the page being wider than the screen of the device, meaning the centre of the page is to the right. Is there CSS code I can apply to fix or is this problem not css related?

www.unitedbyform.com is the site. we tried on both and iphone and android and encountered the same issue. </description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2015 04:55:15 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12713496</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Purchases themes</title>
      <description>i have Purchased this themes Regale 2 , Madison 2  for stiniroehrs.com , but i dont have koken installed  in this domain any amore and i cant unistall the themes and i want to use them for the enoughsaid.org

and iget this message :

Before you can install this item, the Koken installation at stiniroehrs.com needs to be upgraded.

any help ?</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 16:03:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12709802</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regale 1</title>
      <description>Dear Support!

I wanted to use the theme regale as one of my friends is using it and I really like the layout and the style of the theme. 
Unfortunatelly regale 1 is not avaliable anymore on the store. After looking through some older forums and questions, I have found a link, provided by one of your colleagues, and downloaded it. After properly installing it the theme shows up in my theme gallery, but after trying to applying it, it wont load. 
On the preview page I only see a black screen.
Is there any way for me to be able to use this theme, or only the paid version, regale 2 is avaliable?

Thank you in advance!
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2015 10:03:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12634741</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Repertoire custom logo alignment</title>
      <description>I'm having problems getting the custom image logo to vertically align to match the bottom of the primary menu - how do I best do this?  I've kind of hacked it together with a margin-top: 13px; custom css that is applied to header.top div.row div.four.columns nav ul.k-nav-list.k-nav-root but that doesnt seem to always match exactly depending on browser and device page width</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 18:44:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12627931</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Twice to buy the same theme with the same account</title>
      <description>How is that possible? 
Since I have several sites but always the same e-mail address should be at all possible this yet.</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 14:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12606169</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Problem purchasing theme - account not accepted</title>
      <description>I singed into my account to purchase the theme, for the koken installed in cloudways and it says to wait for my account to be accepted, which i am still waiting as I hope to use the new theme ASAP. Please help to expedite ! Thanks!!</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 14:04:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12590690</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Draft lost</title>
      <description>Hi there,
Just a suggestion. It would be great if there was a draft history, instead of only having the previous draft available.

I had a draft that for some reason reverted back to default, so the draft seems to have been lost.

Thanks</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 14:32:51 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12376214</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pulse slideshow after going into an album is it possible?</title>
      <description>Hello :-)

If i click onto an album thumbnail i see the list of the album photos. After that, if i click onto a picture, a "simple" slideshow ist visible.

I would like that immediatly start the pulse slideshow with the pictures of the album.

How can i do that?

Thanks

Charlyn</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 07:29:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12357264</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madison theme navigation</title>
      <description>Hello, on the Madison theme, I would like to change the color/size of the text of the Set of the album. Can I do this in the Custom CSS section and how?

Thanks,
J</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 18:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12325692</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mouse over effect</title>
      <description>Is there a possibility to have a mouse over effect on an image?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 18:43:34 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12303632</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madison</title>
      <description>The arrows (top right) for the navigation from one photo to the next photo does not work (try it: http://photos.xbopp.com/koken/albums/2015-04-30/). It work's for the first 2 photos and that's it. Therefore the theme has lost it's functionality. I have cleared the cache, I have uploaded everything again, but nothing helps.</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2015 13:57:48 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12286415</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Better Panorama Pictures</title>
      <description>Hello

Long Pictures like Panoramas are to small. Please optimize that! Thank you!

Here a picture so you can see what i mean. It looks like an bad joke :-)
http://666kb.com/i/cykmppd49btwlkca6.jpg

Thank you!</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 09:28:22 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12243428</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zoom into Pictures on mobile Devices</title>
      <description>Hello

I use the Axis2 Theme, an on mobile Devices, i can click on the pictures for fullscreen. but i cant zoom in. </description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 16:41:45 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12240825</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>File Suffixes (Types)</title>
      <description>Hi

I am building a custom theme and want to detect when the current content object in an album is a gif. I can get the filename, but I can't think of way to test the filename suffix using Koken lens tags.

Is this possible, any helpers greatly appreciated?

Regards
Mike
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 18:13:02 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12239340</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Main Page slideshow in Repertoire does not diplay pictures at their native size.</title>
      <description>Hello.

Your article about editing theme slideshows says :
 "Expand" automatically expands and contracts the slideshow's height to present all images at their native size.

The native size of my pictures in the library are 433 x 650 / 650 x 433.
But the slideshow displays them at larger dimension and the quality suffers from upscaling.

Is there any way to display them at there native size with the slideshow?</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2015 16:08:28 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12159862</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theme Customization</title>
      <description>Where can I find someone with experience to hire to customize my theme?</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 18:58:12 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/12029286</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>title attributes and filenames</title>
      <description>Hello,

I am using Boulevard Theme. I was wondering if there is a way I can set the imported images to automatically add the file name / alt tag to the caption. This would be great as I have large volumes of images to upload and adding the image titles for each image is not convenient at all for my workflow...

Are the theme template files available to edit incase inserting some php into the span would be the best solution?

Any ideas would be great to know !

Thank

david 
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 09:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11699088</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Translation possibilities</title>
      <description>Currently I have a mixture between english tamplate and german content.

Look on http://zugegensein.de/essays/2015/05/hommage-a-barbara/

At the bottom of the page you read "see more", but just two lines below "Kategorien" because I'be translated this in the backend.

The same with featured images: http://zugegensein.de/featured/das-buch/
You can see newer featured older for navigation on top of the page.

I need more options for translation!

Best regards,
Marc</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2015 10:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11695033</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Image releflection Boulevard image strip</title>
      <description>Hey!

I am using the Boulevard theme (it's great and Koken is very easy to use for my client, thank you for that!). I do have a question/request. Is it possible to have a reflection beneath the images of the Strip? I've seen it at some Wordpress themes. Thanks in advance!

Greets,

Joost</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2015 07:46:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11689039</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Axis 2 Website name</title>
      <description>Hi,

I have a Problem with the way axis displays the website name. When I look at my website on a cell phone everythins is fitted to the resultion of the screen. Except the website name. This is cut of on the right side,</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 13:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11688741</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>I nee the refund!</title>
      <description>Koken was suggested by a friend and after take a look on that I installed it with enthusiam. Immediately  purchased the Regale 2 theme  but after installing it I discovered it doesn't work. Probably due to limitattions on my host for what concerning loopback connection. Brad asked me the login data to investigate on it but never heard back anything else. As was impossible to build my photo site with koken I was forced to turn on another solution. Then I asked for a complete refund because the theme is unusable on my host. After several requests by email and than through paypal I haven't received any reply. I believe its a really unprofessional beahvior.

Damiano</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 12:25:59 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11686150</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Set Covers</title>
      <description>Is it possible to have a set cover as an image that is not in the set? I have diptychs in my set, but would ideally like just one image from a diptych as the cover image. I'm using Axis 2. Thanks!</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 13:14:20 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11678568</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Custom CSS</title>
      <description>Hi there,

First I would say how pleasant is Koken CMS.
In few hours, I can do what I previously do in days...

I'm trying since this morning to customize CSS in Regale 2 theme. 
Everything is fine, except h1 title font size.
I can't change the font size of cover h1. I can change line space, line height, color, not the size.
With firebug, I can see that font size is set to a strange 65.4166666666667px size.

here is a link:
http://didier-oberson.ch/photography/sets/architecture/

Thanks for your help

Didier
</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 13:16:21 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11674480</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madison 2 - Frontpage images not correct loading</title>
      <description>Hello!
I tried to reach you on twitter with this issue, but got no response. 
Please take a look into my tweet (https://twitter.com/timscha/status/592756556967600128)

Sometimes images on Madison 2 Homepage will not load correctly. They will be displayed very small. I have this issue tested on the current versions of chrome and firefox.

Any help would be great,
Tim</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2015 13:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11669265</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Theme and Plugins</title>
      <description>Hey Guys,

ive reinstall my koken on my root server,
now i want to reinstall my theme (Regale2) and my puchased Plugins.

But it doesn't work...
ill press "reinstall" and it loads and loads into the death....
pls help me ! :)

Greetz

TF</description>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 21:31:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11666667</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to remove dash from page title</title>
      <description>I try to edit my page title. I know that i can do this in "site publishing" but i want to remove dash. Now it's like "home - page title" How can i remove dash?</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 01:15:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11662082</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Files affected by the Elementary update contact form</title>
      <description>I customized the Elementary theme. 
To avoid having to redo this customization on the update of the theme (version with contact form), can you tell me what exactly are the files updated in this new version ?

Thank you</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 11:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11654396</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>mobile optimization / Googles new</title>
      <description>Is there any specific mobile optimized themes? 

With google's new update they will be giving better ranks to mobile optimized sites. 

https://www.google.com/webmasters/tools/mobile-friendly/

</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2015 00:38:23 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11651116</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Regale2 Splash front page does not load pictures</title>
      <description>Hello,

My front is a splash sideshow but it does not display any pictures on firefox, on tablet or some mobile, IE, 
only ok on google chrome.

I tried to reset by deleting the front page but it's still the same

any ideas?

thanx a lot for yout help

(franckchemin.fr)</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Apr 2015 06:09:01 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11646383</link>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Madison free theme no longer available?</title>
      <description>Hey, 

I had an installation of koken on my hosting and lost it. I had to re install everything. I used to have my site on Madison theme and now it appears to be no longer available. Is that the case ? 

What can I do ? Is there a chance you can let me install the last version of madison theme? 

Thanks in advance,

J</description>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2015 18:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
      <link>http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/questions/11636173</link>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
